For three metrics and
a confidence level of 95% the answer
was one minus 0.95 cubed.
In general the overall probability
of at least one false positive,
which I'll call alpha overall, will
be one minus the confidence level for
that test, raised to the nth power.
The confidence level is equal to
one minus the individual alpha.
And N is the number of
metrics you are measuring.
Again, this formula
assumes independence.
Thus in the first case the answer
is 1 minus 0.95 to the tenth.
Which is 0.401.
And in the second case, the answer
is one minus 0.99 to the tenth.
Which is 0.096.
So with a 95% confidence level,
the overall chance of a false
positive is quite large.
Getting close to half, and
even the 99% confidence level
isn't enough to limit the overall
chance of an error to 5% or less.
It's closer to 10%.
This plot shows the overall alpha.
That is, the chance that any metric
shows a false first as the number of
independent metrics being tested for
three different confidence levels.
Alpha equals 0.1, 0.05, and 0.01.
For alpha equals 0.01 or 0.05.
The over all alpha blows up quickly.
By the time you have five metrics
with an individual alpha of 0.05.
Your overall alphas almost a quarter.
One alpha equals 0.01 or
99% confidence level.
The overall the alpha looks more
manageable by comparison, but like you
just saw if you have ten metrics you
have a total false positive rate of
almost 105 and that keeps steadily
going up as you increase to 20 metrics.