You've already interacted with the HTML in
a Wikipedia page via your browser's developer tools.
Now, let's figure out how to get that HTML into Python,
so we can work with it programmatically.
I'll start with an internet search for,
"Python request web page from a URL."
Okay. This first link looks like it's from the Python three docs, which is great.
I'll click it and see what it says.
Let's take a look.
This yellow box stands out.
The requests package is recommended for a higher level HTTP client interface.
High level is probably what we want.
Let's try to keep things simple for a first attempt at getting a page from the web.
I think I'll try using the request package.
Okay, the docs for the request package are a little bit silly.
It's says, "Safe for human consumption," so that's reassuring, I think.
Here's a simple bit of code to get us started.
I'm going to try it because request is not part of the standard library,
I'll need to get it installed first using pip, pip3 install requests.
Okay, that's now installed.
Great. Now, I'll fire up the Python interactive interpreter to test the example code.
I'll copy the format of this code to get
the HTML for the Wikipedia page on the dead parrot sketch.
First, I import requests,
I'll call the variable response,
it's a bit more descriptive than they are in the example,
response equals requests dot get parenthesis and inside the parenthesis
I will put the URL for the Wikipedia page on the dead parrot sketch.
The example code shows several things I can do to
get information after this response object.
But what I really want,
is to see the HTML of the page itself that's held in the text attribute of the response.
Let's print it to have a look.
Okay.
Wow, that's a lot of content on this page.
I recognized some of the tags we might expect to see,
there's an anchor tag,
and there's a div,
but it's a little difficult to read this.
It's much more difficult than just looking at the rendered page itself.
So, it looks like a lot of text but let's just
check what type this response.text actually is.
Okay, it's just the string that contains all the HTML of the Wikipedia page.