We just covered a ton of information in this lesson.
We looked at using git add to stage content.
We used git commit to actually commit changes to the repository.
We also looked at what makes a good commit message.
Then we learned about how helpful git diff can
be to help us recall changes that haven't been committed yet.
And last, we just looked at the git ignore
file to tell git what files it should not track.
You now know how to create or clone a repo,
how to make professional commits with
clear descriptive commit messages and then how to review existing commits.
With this knowledge, you can jump in and start working on any git repository.
One powerful concept, we'll look at in the next lesson is branching.
Branching lets you work on a project in multiple different states
and it will take your git skills to the next level. Let's go check it out.