Let's wrap up.
What are the main things we've learned?
>> First you need to check.
Double check, triple check that your
experiment was set up properly.
Look at your end variance.
Check that your experiment metrics
are actually looking sane.
Right, you have to check that before
you try and do anything else.
>> And remember you aren't just
looking for statistical significance.
You're really making
a business decision.
So what if you have an experiment that
statistically significantly improves
the experience for 30% of users but
it's neutral for everyone else.
Do you necessarily want
to launch it as it is or
do you want to try to make it better.
And what if you're in a situation
where it improves things for 70% but
makes it worse for 30%.
So you actually need to make a decision
about whether you want to launch
the feature as it is, or if you
want to try to fine tune it first.
>> And you can't actually forget
the overall business analysis as well.
For example, what's the engineering
cost of maintaining the change?
Are there customer support or
sales issues?
Overall what's the opportunity cost if
you actually choose to launch the change
relative to the rewards you're going
to get from from the change or
potentially not launching the change?
This is all about the judgment
call with regards to
the user experience and the business.
And ultimately that's what your
commission has to be based on.
>> That makes sense,
any other last thoughts?
>> Well, if you haven't actually tested
your change on all traffic, even if it
only impacts a small slice, now's a good
time to test for that incidental impact.
>> Yeah and
if this is the first experiment you run,
especially if it's a really big or
important feature,
you might want to actually try running
a couple of different experiments.
Analyzing the results and then seeing
how you feel about the results of
your first experiment before
you decide to launch it.