Congratulations.
You've reached the end of another course.
You are a version control pro.
But remember that you get better at something the more you do it.
So why don't you practice your new skills on
an open source project by adding to
the documentation or by supplying a code example or two.
You could even translate the material into your native language.
Check the links below for some info on how to get
involved and start collaborating with others.
So maybe you found this all easy or maybe you found the material somewhat challenging.
But the important thing is that knowing these skills and
techniques is the first major step in how to collaborate effectively.
The web is built through collaboration by people all over
the world and now you have those skills to join those ranks.
So keep going. I can't wait to see what you build.