We have talked about how to choose
both our unit of diversion and
our population.
What's next?
>> Next, we have to actually
size our experiment and control.
Now, the key thing to keep in mind is
that this is an iterative process.
What we're going to do is we
are going to try out some decisions for
our unit of diversion and our
population, see what the implication is
on both the size as well as
the duration of our experiment.
And then if we don't
really like those results,
we'll need to revisit our decisions and
iterate.
>> Sounds good.
Where do we start?
>> Well, it makes sense to start
with the sizing process, and
we'll look back at what we
learned in lesson one, and
then revisit it based on what
we've talked about since then.
>> From there we'll discuss some of
the other design considerations,
what the duration of the experiment is,
what the risk factors are and
all of those types of decisions.