Congratulations, you
finished lesson five.
In this lesson we covered the
fundamentals of the handling the results
of your experiment.
Some gotchas for single and
multiple metrics.
And suggestions for
converting significant results into a
real business case for your experiments.
>> This is also the end of the course.
We hope you enjoyed it.
And we want to hear what you thought.
Please go to the forums and tell us what
was your favorite part about the course.
And do you have any suggestions for
what we could improve?
>> Absolutely and now that you have all
the basic pieces try it out on your own.
Experiment and see how it works.