All right, now we'll go through
an example of how to actually check
an invariant and see whether it's
reasonably close between the control and
experiment groups.
Let's say you run an experiment for
two weeks, and
your unit of diversion is a cookie.
So, the first sanity
check you want to do
is to see whether the number of
cookies in the control group
is roughly the same as the number
in the experiment group.
So you get the number of cookies
in each group in each day and
the results look like this.
This column has the number of cookies
in the control group for week one.
This has the number of cookies
in the experiment group.
And this table is the same numbers but
for week two.
Now the first thing I'll do is compute
the total number of cookies for
each group, and
see if the overall division looks even.
If so, great.
If not, then I'll look at
the day by day breakdown.
It turns out that the total number of
cookies in the control group is 64,454,
and the total for
the experiment group is 61,818.
Now, there are more cookies in the
control group than the experiment group.
But, the question is,
is this within what we expect?
Ignoring the day-by-day data for a
minute, how would you figure out whether
the difference between the total
number of cookies in the control and
experiment groups is
within what you expect?
Remember, each cookie is randomly
assigned to the control group
with probability 0.5, and to the
experiment group with probability 0.5.
So, the question is whether
it's surprising that out of
the total number of cookies, 64,454
were assigned to the control group.
Take a few minutes to think about
how you would solve this problem and
write the steps you would
take in plain English.
Then share how you would solve
the problem on the forums.
Again, take a minute to read the post
left by the person before you and
compare their steps to yours.
When you're ready to move on,
check this box.