Okay.
Suppose you're considering another
experiment and you've computed the size
needed to be 1 million pageviews,
split across control and
experiment groups.
If your average traffic per
day is 500,000 pageviews,
then even if you split all of your
traffic evenly between the control and
the experiment groups, you'll need
to run the experiment for two days.
However, is your traffic
really the same everyday?
It's more likely that you have some
weekly variation such as in this graph,
where the traffic is lower on
the weekends and higher on the weekdays.
And if you look at your
metric of interests,
you might see a variation in that based
on what day of the week it is also.
In such a case, you should run on
a mix of weekend and weekday days.
That is you wouldn't want to just
run the experiment on two weekdays.
And then you might need to run for
three days rather than two to get enough
traffic, since the weekends
don't have as much traffic.
And if the change is risky enough
that you don't want to expose
such a large percentage of your traffic
to it, you might run for longer say,
seven days with a lower percentage
of your traffic diverted.