If you're doing diversion
based on the user ID,
the user would be assigned to
a group when they first logged in.
And that assignment would not change.
Note that you can't assign the user
to a group based on their user ID
before they sign in.
That means you wouldn't be able to
run the experiment on this event, so
it wouldn't be in the experiment
group or the control group.
If you're doing cookie-based diversion,
you'd make a decision when
the user first visits the home page, and
again when they start the mobile app,
since they will have a different
cookie on their mobile device.
If the user never clears their cookies,
then this is the answer.
But, they could clear their
cookies at any point,
meaning that they could be
reassigned at any other point also.
If you did event based diversion, then
on every single event, you'd re-decide
whether that event was in the experiment
group or the control group.
And each event could have
a different decision.
If you are doing device
id based diversion,
then you'd assign the group at
the start of the mobile experience.
Since you don't typically
have device id's for
non-mobile devices, you wouldn't
be able to run the experiment on
the events before the user
switched to their mobile device.