Okay.
So we've talked about how to choose and
characterize metrics to evaluate for
your test.
And presumably you know what change or
changes you want to test.
Now it's time to really apply what
you've learned in working through
the decisions you need to make in
actually designing your experiment.
First, we'll need to decide how you
define what you use as a subject in your
experiment and in your control.
In other words, what are the units in
the population that you're going to be
running the test on and comparing?
We call this the unit of diversion.
Next, we'll need to
choose the population.
You'll need to decide which
subjects are eligible.
Everyone?
Only subjects in the U.S.?
When you're testing how to change and
computing the evaluation metrics,
you need to ensure that
you're doing the test and
computing the metric on
equivalent populations.
Then we'll use those decisions and what
we learned in lesson three to properly
size your experiment, before concluding
with a few other decisions you need to
finalize your experiment design,
such as the duration of the experiment.