We just saw that targeting your
experiment to the appropriate traffic,
for example,
to just the English speaking traffic,
can reduce the size of your experiment.
But you mentioned earlier that you might
not always know beforehand what will
be affected.
Right?
>> Yeah.
So
the first reason you don't know
is that you just don't know.
So, for example, if you design
an improvement to your web page and
you don't know which browsers
are really going to benefit the most or
the least from it, that's something
that happens fairly frequently.
Or, you could have a feature on
your site like language detection,
where it classifies it as a language,
if say, the number of search results in
that language is higher than
the number in some other language.
These are things which can
be fairly hard to predict,
exactly, how many of your users
are going to be affected.
You may be able to ballpark it,
but it can be harder to actually
target that experiment directly.
Now the other thing you want
to think about is, you know,
how are you actually
going to detect impact?
If you have a feature that triggers
in a certain way, if it's a really
obvious UI feature, then you know how
many people were actually exposed to it.
But if it's something that happens
on the back end, you know,
do you trigger this particular
feature in generating recommendations?
You actually want to keep track
of what your metric is for, hey,
they should have been
exposed to my feature, and
they actually were
exposed to my feature.
>> Okay.
And then
what effect does that have on
the size of the experiment?
>> Well if you really don't know what
fraction of your population is going to
be affected, you're going to have
to be pretty conservative when you
plan how much time and how many
users have to see your experiment.
Now that said, what I like to do
is either run a pilot where you
turn on the experiment for a little
while and see who's affected, or
you can even just use the first day or
the first week of data to try to get
a better guess at what fraction of your
population you're really looking at.