We're using git to keep track of our projects.
Now that's great for working locally,
but to be able to share this local repository with others,
we'll need another tool.
The tool we'll be using is GitHub.
GitHub is a service for hosting version control repositories.
Now even though their names are very similar,
git and GitHub are quite different.
Git is the tool you use to manage
the repository and you use git primarily on the command line.
Now GitHub is the hosting service which you typically interact with inside your browser.
We'll send a copy of our local repository up to GitHub.
This copy is not on our local machine,
so it's called a remote repository.
The main commands we'll be looking at in this lesson are:
git remote - to manage the remote repository,
git push - to send changes up to the remote,
and then we'll be looking at git pull which will
retrieve updates from the remote repository.
These commands, push and pull,
might not make a lot of sense at first,
but think of these from the standpoint of your local machine.
You've got changes in your local repository that you want to be in the remote repository,
so you'll push the changes to the remote.
But if there are changes on the remote repository that you want in your local one,
you need to pull those changes down.
So these are the three commands we'll be looking at in this lesson.
Let's start out by digging into what a remote repository actually is.