Okay.
In the lessons up to now,
you've figured out what metrics
to use to evaluate your change.
You've characterized those metrics,
you've designed and
at least preliminarily
sized your experiment.
Now that you've run your experiment,
something we're not really
covering the mechanics of here,
you want to see what you can conclude
from the data that you've captured.
In this lesson, we'll go over how
to analyze the results from your
experiment, and determine what you
can and what you cannot conclude.
We'll start with the sanity checks we've
discussed before, and then look at how
to handle evaluation, whether you
have a single or multiple metrics.
Finally, we'll talk
about analysis gotchas.
As always, remember that running
A/B tests is an iterative process.
What you'll learn from this lesson may
inform the steps that you've done up
to now in designing your test as well.