There are a number of version control systems out there,
but three of the most popular are Git, Subversion and Mercurial.
Not only are there dozens and dozens of different version control systems,
there are actually two different categories.
There's the centralized model and then the distributed model.
In a centralized model there's one all powerful central computer that hosts the project;
every interaction must go through this central computer.
In the distributed model there's no central repository of information.
Each developer has a complete copy of the project on their computer,
which is cool because that means you can also work off line.
In this course we'll be using the version control system Git,
which is a distributed version control system.
Now, you might have heard of Git hub.
Git and GitHub are quite different.
Git, is the version control tool,
while GitHub is the service that hosts Git projects.
To work with Git projects you're not required to use GitHub,
but it's an awesome tool and you should definitely check it out.
For now, you can think of it as basically,
just another computer where you can upload a copy of your project.
Centralized, distributed, if these
don't make a lot of sense right now, that's totally fine.
This is to give you a big picture idea of where things fit together.
These terms are more important if you're working with a team but
you'll be working locally on your computer for the entirety of this course.