When I was first learning Git,
one of the hardest things for me to pick up on were all the various terms that were used.
For those of you that see a big long list of terms and zone out,
don't worry, just skim the list for big picture ideas.
If you're like me and like knowing the terms that are being used,
then this section's for you.
These terms are the vocabulary we use to talk about version control,
features of a version control system,
changes we like to make to our code while it's in a version control system, and so on.
Some terms are, well,
version control system, source code manager, commit,
repository, repo, checkout, working directory, staging area,
the index, staging index, SHA, branching,
merging, merge conflicts, remotes.
Get these things out of here.
So yeah, the terminology can be a bit overwhelming.
There are a number of good handouts around the web, though,
but I've created one for you that lists
the most important terms along with a brief definition as a companion to this course.
I highly recommend that you download this right now.
Place it on your desktop, or print it out and have it on your desk.
Use it as we progress through the course to review key terms.
At first, the words might not make any sense
because this is one of those chicken and egg scenarios.
Should I learn the terminology first or how to actually use Git?
I think it's easiest if you learn Git if
you have some familiarity with the terms it uses.
In addition, it might be helpful for you to create your own cheatsheet.
If you get stuck on a word or idea, just write it down.
So if you get a handle on version control's somewhat foreign terminology,
you're already a giant step towards becoming a Git master.