Okay, we know how to calculate pooled
standard error and confidence intervals.
Are we ready to run the experiment?
>> Not quite.
So, we first have to
design our experiment.
Now, the main question
that we have to decide is
given that we have control over how
many page views go into our control and
our experiment, we have to decide
how many page views we need
in order to get a statistically
significant result.
This is called statistical power.
Now, the key thing is that if
we see something interesting,
we want to make sure that we have enough
power to conclude with high probability
that the interesting result is,
in fact, statistically significant.
Now, the key thing to keep in mind is
that power has an inverse trade-off
with size.
The smaller the change that you want
to detect, or the increased confidence
that you basically want to have in
the result, means that you have to run
a larger experiment, so more page views
in your control and your experiment.