I'll test the link extraction code on this article about PICALM,
which is a protein, apparently.
I'll go through the process of downloading and
soupifying the HTML again with this article.
Using the up key on my keyboard saves me a lot of time.
Hmm. So the first link in the article is to the protein article,
but our code found the sling to geneontology.org.
What went wrong? Let's think about it.
It took me a few minutes of searching,
but I eventually found the geneontology link here in the sidebar.
When I look at this anchor tag in the developer tools,
I see that it's part of a paragraph and that paragraph is part of the div we care about.
This is technically what we asked Beautiful Soup for,
but this isn't the link we want.
Let's look at the link we do want,
protein, so we can guess why Beautiful Soup didn't find it.
OK. So the protein link is inside of a paragraph tag,
and the paragraph tag,
if we scroll up far enough,
is also inside of the content div.
But this protein link comes farther down the HTML document than the infobox does.
So even though the infobox is
a distant descendant of the div compared to the protein link,
Beautiful Soup found it first.
It seems like this problem is more complicated than we assumed.
We're not just looking for the first link in the first paragraph,
we're looking for the first link that's in the first paragraph
that isn't also part of an infobox or something weird like that.
Let's go back to the Beautiful Soup documentation
and see if there is any mention of a situation like this.