Okay, now we've estimated
the click-through probability of
the Start Now button, but we haven't
actually changed the button yet.
Once we do that, and
we run the experiment,
how will we analyze the results?
>> Well, there's a concept in statistics
called hypothesis testing, or inference,
which is a quantitative way to establish
how likely it is that your
results occurred by chance.
So, the first thing we need is what's
called a null hypothesis, or a baseline.
In our case, that's the theory that
there's no difference in click-through
probability between our control,
and our experiment.
Then we need to think about what's
called the alternative hypothesis.
Are we interested in whether
the click-through rate is different?
Or just whether it's higher, or lower?
Or are we interested in any
kind of difference at all?