Here are the configuration file that I've downloaded and unzipped.
I need to move these files into the home directory.
The easiest way is to right click on the window and
choose Git Bash Here from the list of options.
This option shows up because I've already installed Git on this machine.
In the shell, just type cd and press enter.
This moves the shell to the home directory.
To open this director in Windows Explorer,
type start and a period.
I like being able to jump to this directory,
so I'll pin this to the quick access menu.
To do that right click on quick access and choose "Pin current folder to Quick access".
Now let me shift these windows around to organize them better.
Now that we have the home directory open,
we can move the configuration files over.
Select both items and drag them to the home directory window.
They're in the correct location.
Now they just need to be named correctly.
Both files need to have a dot at the beginning of their names.
Since Windows rename feature doesn't allow that,
we have to do it on the command line.
We'll use the mv command to rename bash_profile to.bash_profile.
We'll do the same thing with the folder.
We'll use the mv command to
rename you udacity-terminal-config to.udacity-terminal-config.
To see the changes we'll have to open a new shell.
So the shell is now configured with the correct content,
but I also like having a white background with black text,
so I click in the top left corner of the app,
choose options, and then update
the foreground color to black and the background color to white.
Perfect. Now everything is configured.