If everything goes as planned,
this first change won't have
any user visible changes.
So, it wouldn't be risky at all.
In practice though,
if this kind of change goes wrong,
the effects could be huge.
Your site might go down,
or not work at all.
Of course, you should always be testing
changes like this, and all changes
in the controlled development
environment before exposing it to users.
But, sometimes new bugs appear when
the change is exposed to real traffic.
Because of this, it's often a good
idea to roll out this kind of
a change to a small percentage of users,
and
make sure nothing goes wrong,
before rolling it out to everyone.
The second case is low risk.
Changing the color a button is innocent
enough that even if all your users saw
the change, it would probably be fine.
But, of course, as always,
you should still test the change
before rolling it out to users.
The third case is higher risk,
particularly if you end up not
rolling out the experiment.
How are you going to deal with all
these Facebook logins that you're not
supporting?
Keeping the affected users
to a small number, so
that you won't have very many of these
to deal with, would be a good idea.
Finally, assuming that you've run
similar experiments in the past,
this last case is low risk also, since
most users won't notice ranking changes.
If this is the first time
you've tested a ranking change,
though, then this might be risky for
the same reason as the database change.
If there's a bug, the courses might
not appear at all, for example.