Let's squash the last three commits together with git rebase -i HEAD~3.
Now this displays the last three commits that we made in our project.
One thing to notice is that these are in reverse chronological order.
So this one here at the bottom is actually our most recent commit.
Now let's look at each of these columns here.
This last column is the commit message.
This middle column is the commits show.
Now this first column is where you type the command
that you want git rebase to actually perform.
Git rebase is actually a very powerful tool and has a number of commands.
Those commands are listed down here.
We can see that right now these are all listed as pick,
so pick means use this commit.
So if we save this file and quit right now,
each one of these three commits would be saved.
So even though we are rebasing and wanted to squash our commits,
if we left these as pick,
all three of these would exist but they would actually have different shows.
Now lahm wants us to squash our last three commits into one,
and that's actually one of the commands.
S down here or we could just type out the whole word squash.
Squashing uses the commit but combines it into the previous commit.
So we'll take this commit and will type out s for squash,
this one will change to squash,
and this one we couldn't switch this to squash
either because there is no previous commit to this one.
So this would cause an error, so we actually have to leave this one as pick.
Now, if we used these commands right here- pick squash and squash,
it would take these two commits and squash them into this one,
but it would use this commit message.
That's going to be a bit misleading since it's actually
adding destinations for Florida, Paris, and Scotland.
So instead of using this commit message we want to be able to reword the commit message,
and there's actually a command for that.
That's reword or just r. So I'm going to switch
pick to just r. Let's go over this one last time.
We have r here, so we're going to reword this commit message.
So we're going to keep this commit,
but we're going to change the commit message.
The s here means we're going to squash this commit into the previous one.
And the s here similarly means we're going to squash this commit into
the previous one which means it's going to be combined into this one.
So let's save this file and quit the editor to actually do the rebase.
Now, the rebase that we're doing is a multi-step process.
So the first step we have to do is to reword this commit message.
So I'm going to change this to add Richards destination's.
I'll save the file and then quit the editor to continue with rebasing.
So this is the last step of the rebasing.
We can see that this is a combination of the three previous commits.
So these are the commits we're about to squash.
The first commit which is the oldest of the three is the one we just reworded.
Add Richard's destination, and here's the commit message for the second commit,
and here's the commit message for the last commit.
I'm just going to delete all of these.
So it says add Richard's destination as the commit message.
And remember that anything with a hash in front of it is
a comment and it's not included in the commit message.
So we can actually delete these two.
So I'll save the file and then quit the editor to finish rebasing.
And there we go, we rebased the last three commits.
Let's check out the git log real quickly.
We can see here
our include-richards-destinations branch has just one commit ahead of the master branch,
while on the remote repository we actually have these three commits.
So these three commits are the ones that got squashed into this one single commit.
Let's clear the screen for a second and let's try
pushing this branch to the remote repository.
We can see that this push was rejected because
the remote repository has commits that this one does not.
So we need to force push this change through.
And that worked.
Now, this is the pull request page and I haven't refreshed yet.
We can see that the original three commits are listed here and are listed here.
If I scroll down a bit,
we can actually see that I've made a new commit on this pull request.
This is the commit that we just force pushed through.
Now, if I scroll up to the top and refresh the page,
we'll see that all of the numbers change.
Those three commits that were listed here are gone and
this pull request now shows that there's only one commit in the pull request,
which is this one right here.
If we check out the files changed tab we can
see that our changes are exactly the same though,
our css changes here,
and our html changes are here.
Except now they're all combined to just one commit.