I'm on my course-collaboration-travel-plans,
a project that I forked from whams here.
And so, I want my changes to be in this project- in her project.
So I need to send a pull request.
Good thing there's a new pull request button right here.
This is the page where we were able to start a new pull request.
So this is showing us my master branch,
on my repository, compared to the master branch on Lahm's project.
Right now there isn't anything to compare because both of
these branches are pointing to the exact same commits.
So let's switch my branch to the new branch that I just pushed.
So let's go over this one more time,
because this area right here can be a little bit tricky.
This is my project and my branch,
and I'm comparing this change with Lahm's project and her master branch.
And the changes between her master branch and my branch right here are listed down below.
There are three commits on my branch that aren't in her master branch,
and two files have changed.
These are the commits and down here are the files that have changed.
So in this css file these lines were added,
and in the index file these lines were added.
Let's scroll back up here,
and now we can just click on this create pull request button.
So the view has changed a little bit.
Now, we're presented with this form here,
where we can actually send the pull request.
We have the pull request title right here,
which you can see is populated from the same name as the branch name.
So this is another reason why you'd want to name your branches with descriptive names.
I think this is a good pull request title so I'll leave that as is,
and I'm going to write a little message.
Now, this area down here supports markdown.
This looks good to me,
so let's scroll down here and click on the create pull request button.
Notice though, we have now switched away from my project and my page,
I am now on the udacity account,
but looking at lahm's project.
And instead of being on the code tab,
this has switched to the pull request tab,
and it is showing us the conversation here.
Now the conversation includes a little bit of information:
The message I've provided and the commits that I pushed.
And we can see those commits in more detail here.
And then if we want to look at the actual files
that have changed- we can see that on this tab.
Let's switch back to the conversations tab.
Scrolling down, we can see that this branch has no conflicts
with Lahm's base branch or Lahm's master branch,
but we can't do anything with this,
we need Lahm to be able to include
these changes- to include this pull request in her master branch,
because she owns this repository.