Let's start at the beginning,
because it's a very good place to start.
We've got a project with some files,
and we add these files together and make a commit,
and it has this SHA.
Now let's give ourselves a bit more room by
shrinking this down and displaying just the first letter.
Great, so we have this one commit.
Now let's make a few more changes to the project and commit them.
Awesome. So let's say that the most recent commit
that starts with the f is where our project is at version 1.0.
How would we indicate this in git?
We don't want to write this in the commit message.
Perhaps we can list this in the body of the commit message,
but that's not ideal either.
We can use a tag to indicate this.
Tags let you point out particular commits to make them stand out from others,
and we can label the tag with something like v1.0.
Let's add another commit. See how the tag stays locked to a commit?
Let's give ourselves a bit more room.
A tag stays locked to a commit even as more commits are added to the repository.