What changes when you have multiple
evaluation metrics instead of just one?
>> Well one thing that comes up when you
run evaluations of multiple metrics at
the same time,
is that the more things you test,
the more likely you are to see
significant differences just by chance.
So if you're testing 20 metrics, and
you have a 95% confidence level.
You would expect to see one case at
least that time where you got a result
that says it's significant but
it's only concurring by chance.
So this is a problem, but you're not
sunk because it shouldn't be repeatable.
That is if you did the same experiment
on another day or you divide or
just slices or
you did some bootstrap analysis, you
wouldn't see the same metric showing up
as significant differences every time,
it should occur randomly.
There's another technique for
this called multiple comparisons that
adjusts your significance level, so
that it accounts for how many metrics or
how many different tests you're doing.
>> All right when would I use that?
>> One thing a lot of people like to do
an experiment frameworks is do automatic
detection of differences.
So if you're doing exploratory data
analysis you can reanalyze your data and
make sure the same metric isn't
popping up every time and
see if the differences are repeatable.
But if you want to set up say
automatic alerting that tells you,
one of my metrics was significantly
different on this experiment.
You probably want to use multiple
comparisons and there's notes for
that in the instructor's notes.