In the first case, you can't figure out
whether you're carrying all the products
users need by running an A/B test.
You could try carrying a specific
additional product, but if users don't
buy it, you still won't know if there's
a different product you're missing.
Instead, you might want to try asking
users whether there's anything
they feel is missing.
In the second case, you wouldn't be
able to fully test whether the premium
service is a good business
decision using A/B testing.
Users have to opt into
a premium service, so
randomly assigning people to one group
or another wouldn't really work.
You wouldn't have a control
to compare against.
You can still get valuable
information from an A/B test.
For example,
you could see how many users will
read about the additional features or
how many will choose to upgrade
if you make the choice available.
But you can't fully test out the change.
The third case is a great
place to use A/B testing.
There are clear control and
experiment groups, the old algorithm and
the new algorithm.
There are also probably some clear
metrics you could use to evaluate
the change, such as the probability of
a user clicking on a recommendation or
actually watching the movie.
The fourth case may be tricky to test,
depending on whether you have
the computing ability to run both
versions of the backend at once.
If you do though, you can definitely
A/B test the results of the change.
Once again, you have clear control and
experiment groups since
the groups are very comparable.
So, as long as you have
the computing power to
run both simultaneously, you're good.