In the first case, you won't be able
to test this using A/B testing.
People buy cars very rarely, so
it would take too long to see
if you get repeat customers.
And you don't necessarily even have data
about whether customers are recommending
the site to their friends.
The second case seems like it
would be easy to A/B test, and
you certainly could collect data about
user behavior with the new and old logo.
Changing the branding of your company
can be surprisingly emotional for
your users though.
They might need some time to get used to
the new logo, so you wouldn't want to
make a decision based on a short time
window of data collected in an A/B test.
The third case is a great
thing to use A/B testing for.
Once again, there is a clear control and
experiment, and
choosing good metrics to evaluate this
type of change will be much easier
than for the first two cases.
You'll probably be able to choose
something like the probability that
the user progresses
past the initial page.