In the first case, users probably won't
consciously notice if the video load
time is a bit faster or slower, so event
based diversion would probably be okay.
Like Diane mentioned, you may have some
learned effects in this case even if
users don't consciously
notice the change,
in which case you would need to switch
to cookie based diversion, but event
based should be a good starting point,
particularly for a short experiment.
In the second case, it would be pretty
distracting if the button looked
different every time you
reloaded the page, so
event based diversion
wouldn't be a good idea here.
Cookie based diversion
is probably good enough.
If the button looks different on
different devices, that's okay,
since the UI usually looks a little bit
different on different devices anyway.
In the third case, like the first, most
users won't notice ranking changes, so
event based diversion is
a good place to start.
Again, you might need to change this
to cookie based diversion if you notice
a learned effect.
The fourth case is something that
users will almost certainly notice.
Cross-device consistency will also be
important here, if you want to be able
to determine whether the change
impacts the pass rate of the quiz.
If a student watches the video on their
phone, then completes the quiz on their
computer, for example, you'll need them
to be in the same group both times.
Because of this, you'll need to
use user-ID based diversion here.