I'll show you using Google Spreadsheets
to perform the calculations.
First, I'll make a new
column with the differences.
So I'll take equals,
then first group minus the second
group and I'll drag that down.
Next I'll calculate the standard
deviation of the differences,
which comes to about 0.0364.
I'll also calculate the average
which comes to about 0.0043.
So the center of the first
confidence interval is 0.0043.
And the margin of error
is 0.0364 times 1.96.
That is the standard deviation I just
calculated, times the z score for
a 95% confidence level.
That comes to 0.0713.
Then the upper bound of the confidence
interval will be 0.0756 and
the lower bound will be negative 0.0670.
To get the empirical
confidence interval,
I'll sort the rows by difference,
which is in column D.
Then the bounds of the confidence
interval will go from
the second smallest value
to the second largest.
That means the balance of the empirical
confidence interval are negative 0.06,
and 0.08.
The two confidence intervals
are in the same ballpark but
they're not super close.
That's because for the empirical
confidence interval in particular, it's
best to have more than 40 experiments
to be really confident in your answer.