Here's the outline for this course you're taking right now.
Let's click on this link to get to its revision history page.
This main part shows the document that we see in
the normal view but this sidebar provides all the awesome features we want.
This is the history of the changes made to this document.
They're organized by date and show who made the edits.
Clicking on one of these will swap out
the current version of the document with an older one.
Let's click on the October 13 version.
The main area now shows the version of the document as it appeared on October 13.
It also provides these arrows to let us jump to the edits that were made.
The highlight color indicates which user made the edit.
If I like this older version of the document,
I can replace the current version with this older
one by clicking the Restore this revision link.
One last thing is that Google Docs will group
lots of changes together in one larger group.
If you want to see smaller sets of changes,
that's what the, Show more detailed revisions button does.