To see how the click-through-probability
would affect the number of page
views needed,
recall that the standard error depends
on the click-through-probability.
Specifically, the standard error is
proportional to the square root of p
times 1 minus p.
So, for example, if the probability
were 0.5, the standard error would be
proportional to the square root of 0.5
times 0.5, which comes out to 0.5.
On the other hand,
if the probability were either 0.1 or
0.9, then the standard error
would be proportional to 0.3.
It turns out that as your
probability gets closer to 0.5 and
further away from extremes like 0.1 or
0.9, then your standard error increases.
Thus increasing
the click-through-probability but
not above 0.5 would increase
the standard error.
Which means that I'd also need to
increase the number of page views
in order to reduce the standard
error back to its original level.
So now on the online calculator, I'll
try increasing the baseline conversion
rate to 20% and sure enough the sample
size went up to about 6,000.
Now if you increase your
practical significance level,
you're saying you no longer care
about detecting a 2% change.
You would need the change to be
larger than 2% before you cared about
detecting it.
Larger changes are easier to detect, so
you shouldn't need as many page views.
So here I'll try increasing
the practical significance level to 5%,
and the sample size needed goes down
to about 1,000 page views per branch.
If you increase your confidence level,
you're saying that you want to be more
certain that a change has occurred
before you reject the null.
In essence,
you're being more conservative.
You could accomplish that by
rejecting the null less often, but
then your sensitivity would go down.
If you want to keep
sensitivity the same,
you'll need to increase the number
of page views you collect.
So I'll try this out and increase the
confidence level by decreasing alpha.
And, the number of page
views needed has gone up,
now it's about 1,500 instead of 1,000.
Finally, as you've seen before, if you
want to increase the sensitivity of your
experiment, you'll need to collect more
page views to narrow the distribution.
So I'll try increasing sensitivity here,
and
the number of page views needed goes up.
Now it's about 2,000 per group.