Diane, can you tell me more about how to
choose the subject of your experiment?
First, what does that mean?
>> So, what you need to do is you
need to decide how to assign events
to either the control or
to the experiment.
Now what you could do is you could
randomly assign every event.
So for example,
every page view to either the control or
the experiment, but
then if you have a user visible change,
the user's basically going to be like,
oh, I see the change.
They reload.
I don't see the change.
What's kind of going on?
So typically what you want to do for
a user visible change
is that you want to basically
assign people as opposed to events.
Now the problem with online testing is,
what's a person?
Like, how do you actually
determine who a person is?
One obvious example is to use
a user ID like a log in, but
the problem there is,
each person could have multiple log ins.
You know, for example, I have both
a consumer and a corporate account.
Right?
And so, you know, if you're a student,
you could have multiple
different accounts,
if you wanted to try the quiz in
different ways or for whatever reason.
So each person doesn't have
to have a single account.
Now another option is to basically use
an anonymous identifier like a cookie.
This is basically something that gets
assigned to a particular
browser in a device.
Now, again the same issue happens here,
right?
Because this is tied to a single
browser and single device if you change
from your laptop to your mobile phone,
if you change from Safari to Chrome,
in each of those cases,
you're going to be changing the cookie.
And, so in any case, if you're
trying to basically assign a person,
you're going to be using
some imperfect proxy.
Now in each of these cases, whether
you're doing an event based diversion,
a cookie based, or a user ID, these are
all what we call our unit of diversion.
So I think before we sort of discuss the
pros and cons of these, I think you're
going to be going through the details
of what each of these really mean.
>> Yeah.