Now let's look at some different cases
that could have come up in our results.
Here I've drawn our practical
significance boundary as these
two blue lines, and
zero as this black line.
Our point estimate, that is d hat,
for the example we just went over was
greater than the practical
significance boundary.
And in fact, both ends of the confidence
interval were greater than
the practical significance boundary.
Based on this, it's highly probable
that the click-through probability did,
in fact, change by more than
the practical significance level.
Now let's go through some other possible
cases of what your results could look
like, and practice recommending
a decision in each case.
Choose whether you would want to launch
the change, not launch the change, or
try to gather more data,
ideally by running an additional test,
in each of these cases.
The first case is the one you just saw,
and as I said,
I would launch this change.
You should assume that a positive
change in click-through probability
is desirable, and
a negative change is undesirable.
Remember that the goal of running
A/B tests is to gather data to
make a decision.
And the reason we did the work of
computing the power in the confidence
intervals is so that we would
understand how likely it is that our
results are repeatable and robust.
And make the right decision.
Given this, choose the decision
you think is best for each case.