I've downloaded the files and unzipped the directory.
In the Terminal, I'll type cd to make sure I'm in the home directory.
Using the move command,
I'll move the udacity-terminal-config directory into my home directory,
but I also want to rename it by adding a dot at the front.
Since the Terminal is in the home directory,
I'll move this directory into the home directory and name it.udacity-terminal-config.
The bash_profile file also needs to be in my home directory,
but this is a very common file and if I already have this file,
then I don't want to overwrite it.
I'll use ls -a to check if I already have one.
I already have a bash_profile file,
so I'll open it up in my code editor.
Now that I have this file open,
I just need to copy the text out of here into this file.
Now just save the file and I'm done.
If you don't already have a bash_profile file,
then you'd use the move command to move this file into your home directory,
making sure to name it with a dot at the beginning.
But I'm not going to run this because I already have updated my.bash_profile file.
Now even though I've updated my bash_profile,
nothing's changed with the Terminal.
That's because I need to restart it.
So here's what your Terminal should look like.