For the Audacity example, we decided to
use click-through-probability instead of
click-through-rate.
Why, and how do you decide in general?
>> So generally speaking, you use a rate
when you want to measure the usability
of the site, and a probability when you
want to measure the total impact, right?
So if, for example, you want to measure
the usability of a particular button,
you use a rate because the users have a
variety of different places on the page
that they can actually
choose to click on.
And so the rate will say how often
do they actually find that button.
Now, if you just want to know how often
users went to the second level page on
your site, you use a probability,
because you don't want to count if
users just double-clicked, or did they
reload, or all of those types of issues.
>> Okay.
And in our example,
we're interested in whether users
are progressing to the second level of
the funnel,
which is why we picked a probability.
>> That's right.
>> That makes sense.
So, how will we actually
compute the probability?
>> So, to compute the probability,
you're going to have to first just work
with the engineers to
modify your website.
They're going to have to
change the website so
that on every page view
you capture the event,
and then whenever a user clicks
you also capture that click event.
Now, once you have the data captured,
to compute our rate,
you just sum the page views,
you sum the clicks and you divide.
Pretty simple.
For a probability though, you're going
to have to match each page view with all
of the child clicks, so that you count,
at most, one child click per page view.