Because we have two samples,
we'll need to choose a standard error
that gives us a good comparison of both.
The simplest thing we can do is
calculate what is a called a pooled
standard error.
Recall that we'll measure
the users who click in each group,
which we'll call x control and x
experiment, as well as the total number
of users in each group, which we'll
call n control and n experiment.
Now, the first thing we'll calculate
will be what's called the pooled
probability of a click.
And I'm using a hat here because
this is an estimated probability.
And the pooled probability is the total
probability of a click across
groups, that is,
the total number of users who clicked
divided by the total number of users.
Then we'll calculate the pooled standard
error, which is given by this formula.
Now recall that we're going to estimate
the difference between p experiment and
p control, and I'll call this
difference d hat for difference.
Under the null hypothesis d,
the true difference is equal to zero.
Then we would expect our estimation,
d hat, to be distributed normally,
with a mean of zero and a standard
deviation of the pooled standard error.
If the estimated d is greater than 1.96,
our z score,
times the pooled standard error, or
less than the negative of this cutoff,
then we can reject the null
hypothesis as unlikely and
say that our difference represents
a statistically significant difference.