Great job setting up your computer to use GIT.
Going through this lesson you laid a solid foundation to start learning version control.
We looked at the benefits of version control and how incredibly helpful it can be.
You also looked at the terminology that version control systems use.
And you did download the terminology document, right?
It'll be extremely helpful to have on hand as you go through the remaining lessons,
and last you installed GIT and got everything configured. Fantastic work!
Really, a lot of people get bogged down with
all this stuff and never actually learn version control.
So congrats on getting this far.
Now let's head to the next lesson to learn how to create a GIT repository.