Now I want you to assess the participant
risk of a few possible experiments.
For each experiment, choose whether
you think the risk is minimal or
more than minimal.
That is beyond the risks that may
be encountered in normal life.
First, suppose you were on
a search engine such as Bing and
you're testing a change adding
information to your results page.
Specifically for shopping queries,
you're adding price information
available from product sites.
How much risk would this cause
the users of your website?
Second, suppose you've created an app
that helps users monitor their diet,
exercise, and sleep.
you're considering adding a feature
that gives users dietary advice and
lets them know the possible
consequences of their current diets.
For example, your app might let
a user know that their current sugar
intake puts them at high risk for
developing diabetes, and
advise that they eat less sugar.
Would it pose beyond a minimal
risk to test this change?
Finally, suppose you run an online
encyclopedia, such as Wikipedia, and
you want to test changing
the location of the search bar.
What level of risk would this present?
For each change, check the box if you
think testing the change would pose more
than a minimal risk to
the website's users.