Like Diane and Carrie said,
we first need to come up with the high
level concepts for our metrics.
A good place to start is with
the overall business objective.
And what Audacity ultimately cares
about is helping their students get
jobs in finance.
Of course, they also need their
business to be financially sustainable.
That is, they need to make money.
We can break these objectives down
into steps using a customer funnel
like you saw in lesson one.
At that point,
we put four steps into the funnel.
How many users visit the homepage,
how many users explore the site further,
how many create an account, and
how many complete a course.
The idea is that each of these
is a step in the process
of either getting a job or
helping Audacity make money.
In this case, because they might
use coaching at some point.
This funnel is pretty
coarsely grained though.
Can you think of more stages
a student might go through?
Maybe in between some of these steps or
before or after them.
Try to expand the funnel until it
has at least ten total steps, and
put the steps that you've
thought of in this box.
Since Audacity is a hypothetical
company, you can use Udacity or
another online education company
to generate ideas if you'd like.