Now that we've set up a hypothesis test,
how will we decide whether
to reject the null?
>> Well, we're going to need to look at
our conference intervals in a slightly
different way.
So remember in this case,
we actually have two samples.
We have the control side,
which may have a different number
of users from the experiment side.
So we'll need to compare the proportion
of clicks estimated on the control side,
with the proportion estimated
on the experiment side.
Then the quantitative task tells us
whether it's likely that the results we
got, the difference we observed, could
have occurred by chance, or if it would
be extremely unlikely to have occurred
if the two sides were actually the same.