Like Kerry said,
if you think you can identify
what population will be affected
by your experiment, you might want to
target your experiment to that traffic.
That is, only run your experiment
on the affected traffic.
Let's take a look at how this can
affect the variability of your metric.
Just like you saw that changing
the unit of diverging can change
the empirical estimate of variability,
filtering your traffic can
change the variability as well.
For example, suppose you want to control
the change that will only affect users
in New Zealand to see whether it
increases click-through probability.
You run the experiment and looking only
at the New Zealand data, you find that
there were 6021 unique visitors in
the control group, 300 of whom clicked.
There were also 5979 users in the
experiment group, 374 of whom clicked.
Based on this and using
the equations you saw in lesson one,
the estimated probability of
a click in the control group or
the baseline probability is about 5.1%.
The estimated probability in
the experiment group is 6.3%.
And the pooled standard error is 0.0042.
Now suppose you had
analyzed the global data
instead of just the New Zealand data.
Since the change doesn't affect
other traffic, let's say for
the sake of simplicity that in
all the non-New Zealand traffic,
there were 50,000 users in each group
and 2,500 of them clicked in each group.
Now, for the global data,
which includes both the other data and
the New Zealand data added together,
what would be the pooled standard error?
Is this higher or
lower than the pooled standard error for
just the New Zealand data?
Write your answer in this
box to four decimal places.
Also, is there a statistically
significant difference at alpha
equals 0.05 in New Zealand?
How about globally?
Select yes or no in each case.