In the first case, there is probably
no new information being collected,
since the newsletter sign-ups were
already being stored by user ID.
As long as the original data collection
was approved, this should be fine.
The second case though,
depends on exactly how the email
addresses are being stored.
The most natural implementation
would be to store them by cookie,
since the diversion is by cookie.
That would make those
cookies non-anonymous,
which potentially impacts any other
data that is being collected.
For example, if another experiment is
storing data by cookie that you wouldn't
want re-identified, then that data has
now become linked to an email address.
Thus it would be good to seek out
additional review for this experiment.
This is a pretty subtle point, but
in general, you to watch out for
what whether you are accidentally
identifying data that would otherwise
have been anonymous.
The third case does not
require an additional review.
Storing clicks by cookies
is not a problem and
is probably already being
done else where on the site.