Okay, we've just seen some cases
where AB testing isn't very helpful.
What should we do in those cases?
Are there any other
techniques you can use?
>> Well, there are a lot of different
ways to gather data about users.
And, some of them can be
complimentary to running an AB
test eventually, as well.
So, for example, often you'll have logs
of what users did on your website.
You can analyze them retrospectively, or
observationally, to see if a hypothesis
can be developed about what's
causing changes in their behavior.
And, that's something where you may want
to go forward, and actually design, and
randomize, and experiment,
do a perspective analysis.
And, you can use the two data sources
as, to kind of compliment each other.
Where, you may develop a hypothesis
from looking at the logs.
But, you actually want to test out
whether you can make this happen in
an experiment.
And so then, you'll want to run an AB
test as well to compare the results,
and, and see if your theory is valid.
>> There's a whole host of other
techniques as well, ranging from user
experience research, to focus groups,
and surveys, and human evaluation.
Now, what happens is that AB
testing can give you a lot
of broad quantitative data.
But, these other techniques
give you very deep and
qualitative data that are really
complementary to AB testing.
So, for example, you know, these other
techniques can do a better job of
telling you which mountain
you should be on.
So, we'll be going over some of these
other techniques in lesson three.
>> So, there are definitely some things
that are very difficult to test with
AB testing.
So, for example,
if you completely redo your site, or
change the way that
users interact with it.
>> That's something that can be really
hard to run a controlled experiment
with, and we'll talk about
why later in the course.