To calculate the confidence interval,
I'll need the average of the seven
measurements, the standard deviation and
the standard error.
I can compute the average using Google
spreadsheets average function, and
this comes out to about 91,000.
Then I can compute the standard
deviation, using the same strategy but
with the standard deviation function.
And this comes out to about 17,000.
Finally the standard error for the
sample will be the standard deviation
divided by the square root of 7,
which comes to about 6,000.
Rounded to the nearest integer,
I get 91,762, 17,015 and 6,430.
Now, to calculate the confidence
interval, the estimated mean,
or n bar,
will be the center of the interval.
Then I'll need to calculate
the margin of error.
Because this metric is
normally distributed,
the margin of error is the z score
times the standard error, and
since we're using a 95% confidence
interval, our Z score is 1.96,
then the margin of error
comes to about 12,605.
The upper bound of the confidence
interval will be the center plus
the margin of error, which is 104,367.
And the lower bound is 79,158.
So if Audacity repeated
the measurement for
another seven weeks,
they might expect to get anywhere
from 79,000 to a 104,000 as
the mean homepage visits per week