In the first case, Audacity
definitely has access to this data.
But students could take a long time
between completing one course and
signing up for another.
So this metric probably takes too long
to measure during most A/B tests.
In the other two cases,
the companies don't have direct
access to the data they want.
The shopping company doesn't know
how happy its users are, and
the search engine doesn't know whether
users found the information they wanted.
So these two ideal metrics can't
be directly calculated at all.
So the answer is that all of these
metrics would be difficult to
use in an experiment.
Lets talk to Diane and Carrie about
some other techniques you can
use in the type of situation to
get a proxy for what you want.