Now, consider the following
hypothetical AB tests.
If you where planning to run each of
these tests, which cases are the most
ethically concerning according
to the criteria just outlined?
In each case, check the box if you would
seek further review or possibly obtain
user consent, rather than moving
forward without further review.
And first,
suppose you want a news website with
articles that give financial advice
such as whether to invest in index
funds or pick individual stocks.
You want users to take a survey and
answer which of five broad
ranges includes their net worth.
You want to test various methods of
getting users to take the survey.
One method is an option to take
the survey at the bottom of the article.
And another is to prompt the user to
take the survey after reading the first
page, and not allow them to continue to
the second page until they've responded.
Would you seek out further review or
move forward with this experiment?
Next, suppose you work at
a company that delivers meals and
you want to test different
layouts of the menu to see
if users order food more often
with particular layouts.
Would you seek out review in this case?
Finally, suppose your company builds
devices that measure heart rate and
an app that allows users to track their
heart rate during various activities.
You want to test whether different
ways of presenting the heart rate
data leads users to increase
how much they exercise.
Again, check the box if you would
seek further ethical review of
this experiment.