We've used several useful string methods so far,
but where did they come from?
You can learn which methods the different types offer in Python's official documentation.
Here's the count method we just used.
Notice how the documentation mentions two optional arguments, start and end.
You can use these to limit the counts to occurrences
that appear within specified sections of a string.
Throughout the documentation,
optional arguments are indicated with square brackets like these.
Any arguments surrounded by square brackets are optional.
The documentation tends to be terse and precise,
but it's your most valuable resource.
Don't be afraid to use it.
Try out some of the other string methods that are listed in the documentation.
I've included a link to this section of the docs below this video.