The answer in the first case depends
primarily on what information is being
gathered in the survey.
If the survey collects personal
information such as names,
then the information received
in the survey is more sensitive.
However, in most cases,
this survey should be fine to run if
no personal information is collected.
Survey data that doesn't
collect personal information
isn't usually considered sensitive.
Since users can chose to respond
either not at all or dishonestly.
Users can voluntarily
choose what to do and
its this implicit voluntary
consent that's key.
The ethical considerations also increase
if the user can only read the article in
exchange for
their survey information, even if
there is still that voluntary consent.
The mail delivery experiment
is probably fine.
No new sensitive data
is being collected, and
the risk to users of different
menu layouts is minimal.
The heart rate experiment should
probably get additional review.
Since physical fitness is
important to good health,
presentations that confuse
users about their data or
encourage them to exercise too much or
too little could pose a serious risk.
Also, the data being collected
is certainly sensitive and
needs to be carefully secured and
anonymized.
Depending on the data, it may not be
possible to anonymize it while keeping
the same level of granularity in which
case you may need to aggregate the data.