Number of events would be a good
population sizing invariant.
Number of cookies and number of signed
in users would be good as well, for
the same reasons as before.
Cookies are being
explicitly randomized over.
User IDs are typically
larger than cookies,
in the sense that one user ID can
correspond to multiple cookies.
So user IDs should be
evenly split as well.
And it's more likely that the events
could end up unevenly split, but
it's not something you're expecting.
And it would be good to catch
that if it does happen.
The click-through rate on the Start Now
button would not be a good invariant.
By adding a sign-in
button to the home page,
the experiment could affect how many
people click the Start Now button.
Maybe fewer people would click the Start
Now button if they instead signed in and
then went directly to a course
they had already started.
The probability that a user enrolls
in a course would not be a good
invariant either.
Users often enroll in
courses after signing in, so
changing sign in rates
could affect enrollment.
The sign-in rate would definitely
not be a good invariant.
This is the exact metric that Audacity
is trying to change in this experiment.
The video load time would
be a good invariant.
No backend changes were
made in the experiment, and
the user has no control
over a load time.
So, they can't affect it.