At a 95% confidence level or
an alpha of 0.05, the Z-score is 1.96.
I'll multiply this Z-score by each
standard error to get the margin of
error in each case.
Now, for the first case, the margin
of error is smaller than the observed
difference, which means the confidence
interval won't include zero.
So, the difference is significant.
In the second two cases, the margin of
error is also smaller than the magnitude
of the observed difference.
So, these changes are significant also.
In the last case, the margin of error is
wider than the observed difference, so
this is not statistically significant.
Using the Bonferroni method,
I get an individual Z-score of 2.5.
It's actually between 2.49 and 2.5, but
it's closer to 2.5, so i'll use that.
To get this,
I divided the overall alpha of .05 by 4,
and looked up the result
in a Z-score table.
Multiplying this by the standard errors,
I get these margins of error.
Now, it turns out that each margin
of error is now larger than
the corresponding difference, so
none of these metrics have a significant
change using the Bonferroni method.
In this case, the Bonferroni method
is probably too conservative.
If the course description was
an improvement, then it makes
sense that it could cause more than
one of these metrics to move and
they're probably more
likely to move together.