The standard deviation in
this case comes to 0.0029.
And, that means the margin
of error is 0.0056.
The confidence interval balance
are then 0.4944 and 0.5056.
The actual fraction in
the control group is 0.5006.
Which is within what is expected.
So, this does pass the sanity check.
Notice that the actual fraction in
the control group wasn't exactly 0.5.
And looking at the day by day data
again, the number of events in
the control and experiment groups
wasn't exactly equal on any day.
That's expected.
And, since the fraction in the control
group is within the bounds of
the confidence interval,
there's no reason to be alarmed.
Since the total numbers pass the sanity
check this time, there's no need to dig
into the day-by-day data to
figure out what's going wrong.