And for the updated course description,
the primary metric I would want to
track is the probability progressing
from the course list page to the course
overview page for that course.
That's metric 3 on our list over here.
It would also be good to track
continued progression down the funnel.
If the updated description
was accidentally misleading,
you might see an increased click through
rate to the course overview page, but
then a drop off when students realized
the course wasn't right for them.
So it might be good to track the
probability of enrolling in the course,
and if you have time,
maybe even how students
are progressing through the course.
Now by increasing the size of the Start
Now button, you're making the button
more prominent, presumably with the
intention of making it easier to find.
So this is a good time to use
the click-through-rate of the button,
which is metric 1 on our list.
Click-through-probability could
also be a good choice here, but
like Diane mentioned in lesson one,
rates are usually better for
assessing how easy it
is to find a button.
For the experiment making the benefits
of the paid service more clear, the best
metric to use is the probability that
the enrolled students start paying for
coaching, or metric 5.
It would also be good to measure
the user retention over various
time periods.
That is, how long do the students
continue paying for coaching?
Or you might also look
at some usage metrics.
That is, among the students
who are using the coaching,
do they use the coaching more, now that
it's more clear what the coaches can do?