As mentioned previously, a clear
statement of what data you collect and
how you use it, is ethically necessary,
assuming you collect any data
about your users at all.
A history of your company's funding,
on the other hand, is not required.
And while it's probably a good idea for
most sites to have a navigation bar,
this isn't an ethical requirement.
A list of all experiments
might sounds nice, since then,
users can be fully informed about what
experimentation they are undergoing.
However, for some experiments,
giving out this information could skew
your results, and for experiments with
minimal risk that properly protect
sensitive data,
this measure is not necessary.
A search bar, like a navigation bar,
might be a good feature for
many sites to include, but
it's not ethically necessary.