The git rebase comment is a tricky beast.
If you do a search for it on the web you'll see a lot of warnings
about how this command is dangerous and can destroy your repository.
And that isn't a surefire way to prevent you from trying it out,
I don't know what is.
The truth is the tool is powerful and can
wipe out a chunk of your repository in just a few steps,
but it's not as dangerous as you've been led to believe.
It's almost impossible to destroy a git repository when you're using the git commands.
We'll be using git rebase to do something called squashing.
Squashing is just taking a number of commits and combining them into one single commit.
Let's say that you've been working on a new feature in
the last three commits you had were all little typo changes.
With git rebase, you can combine
these three commits into one larger commit. Let's take a look.