A/B testing in technology,
like many experiments in anthropology,
psychology, sociology and
medicine, are on actual people.
Because of this,
you need to ensure that the participants
are adequately protected.
To explain this, let's go through a few
examples of cases where participants
may not have been adequately protected.
One famous example from medical history
is the Tuskegee syphilis experiment,
where approximately 600 rural
African-American men in Tuskegee,
Alabama, between 1932 and 1972,
thought they were receiving free
healthcare from the government.
But in fact, they were being cited
regarding the natural progression of
untreated syphilis.
This study continued even after
penicillin was established
as a standard treatment for syphilis and
the men were both not treated and
not informed of a possible treatment.
Another example from psychology
is the Milgram experiment,
done in the early 1960s,
where Yale professor, Stanley Milgram,
measured the willingness of studied
participants to obey an authority figure
who instructed them to administer
electric shocks to a third person.
That third person was an actor who
simply pretended to be shocked
with gradually increasing responses and
pleas to stop.
The question was, how far would
the participants would go in
causing pain with prompts
from an authority figure?
In both cases, participants were subject
to a high risk for permanent harm.
Untreated syphilis can cost death, and
participants of the Milgram experiment
may have been damaged psychologically.