After creating a new repository,
we're presented with this quick setup page.
The first thing we see is that we can choose either the HTTPS URL or the SSH version.
Clicking on the SSH version changes this URL here and then these URL's down here.
We're just going to switch back to HTTPS.
If you want any information about the SSH URL and
how to work with all that, check below the video.
The next section down here is what to do with a new repository.
We have an existing repository which will look at in just a second.
But if you want to create your remote repository on GitHub you can do that first,
and then you'd follow these commands.
So this first line would create a README file with a simple heading,
then you'd initialized git,
add that README file, commit it,
and then create a link to this remote repository.
We're not going to be looking at the new repository section
since we already have an existing repository, so let's check that out.
Now if you notice these two lines right here are
the exact same one as these two lines right here.
So when you start with a new repository,
you have these initial commands to run and then you run these lines right here.
If you already have an existing repository you would just run these lines right here.
So this first line,
it creates a connection to the remote repository upon GitHub.
We'll look at pushing in the next section,
but for now, just copy the top line and run it in your terminal.