Recall in lesson one, we used the
example of changing the Start Now button
on our online education website,
Audacity, and we use click-through
probability as the metric.
In this lesson, we'll be focusing
on metrics for experiments.
We'll first cover how to define a
metric, which involves brainstorming and
establishing a suite of metrics.
Then taking things from a high
level concept of a metric
to a practical definition that
works given your data capture.
Then we'll explain how to build
intuition about your metrics and
understanding your metrics
sensitivity and robustness.
We'll conclude with how to characterize
the variability of your metric.