In each of the following example
experiments, choose what
unit of diversion you think would be
needed to ensure enough consistency.
That is, if a consistent user
experience is not necessary,
choose event level diversion.
Otherwise, choose cookie diversion,
if that is consistent enough.
And, choose user-id diversion
if that is necessary.
First, suppose Audacity is testing a
change to the backend which would reduce
video load time by 100 milliseconds,
but it would be more expensive.
They want to know whether the reduced
load time will be worth the money.
What level of consistency
would they need in this case?
And second, suppose Audacity has placed
the button more prominently on the page
by changing the color and
increasing the size.
Third, suppose Audacity has a search bar
that lets students search for classes.
And, they test changing the order in
which the search results are shown.
Finally, suppose Audacity notices
a low pass rate for some quizzes, and
they test adding additional
information to the instructor's
notes below the videos before those
quizzes to see if this helps.
In each case, select what level of
consistency Audacity would need.