Branches, merges, and merge conflicts.
Wow, this lesson had a ton of useful information in it.
Branches let us work in isolation from the rest of the project.
Then after you're finished,
you can use Git to merge your branches together.
Now, it doesn't happen all the time,
but if there's a merge conflict,
just pop open your editor and search for the merge conflict indicators.
Remove the lines with the indicators,
figure out what lines you're going to keep,
save the file, stage the file,
and then commit. Easy-peasy.
Congratulations, you are now a Git master.
But if you'd like to learn one last skill,
check out the next lesson where we look at editing,
undoing, and erasing commits.