Diane, I've got data from my experiment.
Can we look at
the click-through rate and
see whether the change
was an improvement?
>> Hold your horsies, there!
Not quite yet.
Before we can look at click-through
rates to determine what happened in your
experiment, first we have to do all
those sanity checks in order to
ensure that your experiment
was run properly.
>> Hm, what kind of sanity checks?
>> Well, there are all sorts
of things that can go wonky,
that could really
invalidate your results.
For example, maybe something went
wrong in the experiment diversion and
now your experiment and
your control aren't comparable.
Or maybe you used some filters and
you set up the filter differently
in the experiment and the control.
Or you set up data capture and
your data capture isn't
actually capturing the events that you
want to look for in your experiment.
Or you know I could just
kind of keep going.
Remember in lesson three when
we talked about counting clicks?
Well all those ways that
counting clicks can go wrong?
We have to test for
all of those before you can look
at the results of your experiment.
>> Okay, how do I test for those things?
>> So do you remember
back in lessons three and
lessons four when we talked
about invariant metrics?
You're going to check those.
And there are really two
main types of checks.
The first one is going to be
the population sizing metrics,
based on your unit of diversion.
Now what you're really checking there
is that your experiment population and
your control populations
are actually comparable.
The other check are those
actual invariants,
those metrics that shouldn't change
when you run your experiment.
And what you want to do is you want
to test that they didn't change.
Now, once you've done those sanity
checks, then, and only then,
should you be doing the more
complicated analysis to determine, hey,
was my experiment good, was it bad,
what's my recommendation going to be?