So far, you've been working on a tame version of Python inside the Udacity classroom.
But in time, you're going to need to be able to run
Python scripts and experiment in the Python interpreter on your own computer.
So it's installation time. Ready?
Go for it.
Python is a popular open-source programming language.
Open-source means that it's free to download, change, and use.
And the fact that it's already popular means there are online instructions to
help you get it installed for most common operating systems.
Because it's popular and open-source,
there's a large global community working on developing Python.
For you, as a Python user,
that means there will be new versions coming out as
Python is improved by the community. Should we try this one?
Okay. You might find yourself needing to update Python from time to time,
especially if you're collaborating with other people as you write
Python programs that are compatible with the version of Python they're using.
Next, we'll introduce you to the Python we're
using so that our code is compatible with yours,
and we'll help you make sure you've got it up and running correctly. Need a hand?
Yes please. One, two, three.
Okay. We've got this one installed. Now it's your turn.