The shuffled cards are not independent.
Since each card appears in the deck
exactly once, as you draw each card,
it gives you information
about the next card.
If the first card is black,
the second is slightly less
likely to be black, and so on.
If your deck were infinitely large,
that wouldn't be a problem, but
drawing 20 out of 52 cards
is a pretty big fraction.
The die rolls are independent.
The probability of success is
one-sixth rather than one-half, but
the probability doesn't
have to be a half for
the binomial distribution to apply.
The events just need to be independent.
And in this case,
each die roll doesn't affect
the outcome of the other die rolls.
The search engine case
is not independent.
Often, if someone doesn't find what
they want the first time they search,
they'll immediately search again
with slightly different words.
Those are two separate events,
but they're not independent.
You would expect the results
to be related in some way, but
you can't necessarily tell that
they came from the same user.
The education case is probably
not exactly independent, but
it's a lot closer.
Each student corresponds to only
one event, not multiple events, and
Udacity students are spread
out all over the world.
You wouldn't expect two different
students to be terribly related.
Of course, there are exceptions.
Maybe some students create two accounts,
in which case,
we wouldn't know that it's
two different students.
Or maybe some take courses with
their friends, in which case,
whether they complete would be
correlated, but in practice,
it would probably be reasonable to
assume a binomial distribution here.
The shopping cart case
is also not independent.
For example, one person could
add several items to their cart,
then purchase all of them.
The outcome for these different
events was highly related.