The first step to sanity checking
our results is choosing a set of
invariant metrics.
Like Diane mentioned, there are two
types of invariant metrics.
Population sizing metrics, and any other
metrics you don't expect to change.
Now, I'm going to describe
two experiments and
for each one, I want you to think about
what metrics should be invariant.
That is, what would be the same in
the control and experiment group?
In the first experiment,
Audacity changes the order of
courses in the course list
to see how much this affects which
courses users eventually enroll in.
The unit of diversion is a user ID
since users may visit the site multiple
times to explore classes before
finally enrolling in one.
In the second experiment, Audacity
changes the infrastructure serving
videos hoping to reduce
the video load time.
This time,
the unit of diversion is an event.
Now, which of the following
metrics would be good invariants?
Number of signed in users,
number of cookies, number of events,
click-through rate or
CTR on the Start Now button.
Remember, this button takes the user
from the homepage to the course list.
Or finally, the time it takes a student
to complete a course on average.
Check each box if that metric would be
a good invariant for that experiment.