When a commit is made,
only the changes that are on the staging index are moved into the repository.
If we want to include the second set of changes in the commit,
then we need to stage the changes.
Now that the second change to the HTML file has been staged,
the two sets of changes to the HTML file are combined into just one set of changes.
And then we can commit like normal to move these changes into the repository.
We have all of these changes saved in our repository,
but how do we access these commits?
What if we want to look at this specific commit?
When each commit is made,
git creates an ID for it.
The ID for the commit is its SHA,
the first seven characters what each commits SHA might look like.