To give you a bit more variety
in the examples you've seen,
I'm going to go over three
more possible changes.
Again, for each one,
check the box if you think it would be
useful to run an A/B test on the change.
First, suppose you have
a website selling cars, and
you're considering a change, and
you want to know wether that
change will make customers more likely
to return or refer their friends.
Second, suppose a company
wants to update their brand,
including the main logo for their site.
Would you A/B test this change?
Third, suppose you want to test some
changes to the initial page of your
mobile application.
You want to change things like
what information is included,
what wording you use,
and what colors you use.
Check each case that you think is
a good candidate for A/B testing.