Let's go over the structure of this course.
First, we'll learn how to work with text and numeric data.
We'll explore Python build-in functions and methods,
so that we can do useful work without having to write lots of new code of our own.
Then, we'll put together these basic parts,
create data structures to hold information,
and write our own functions.
This means you'll be able to write Python programs to automate the things you care about.
For example, watch out scores on a bunch of
individual restaurant of use and tell their overall rating.
It will clean noisy data sets by removing duplicate injuries and sorting them.
You'll get the opportunity to apply
what you've learned to a real life scenario in the lab.
You'll be getting nosy by processing
some phone records and analyzing the patterns you find in them.
The last part of this course will be a bit different.
At this point, you'll know enough Python to write large programs.
So instead of learning more syntax,
we'll focus on how to approach real problems and how to design programs to solve them.
We'll show you how to break problems down into smaller ones.
And Sharon and I will demonstrate this process by writing a web crawler together.
Let's go and learn some Python.