I've got two terminals open and both are located in the blog project.
Let's run git log in this one and git log --oneline over here.
The line holds the information for just one commit.
It's the first seven characters of the Shaw,
and then the commit message.
Here's the Shaw for the most recent commit.
And here's the same commit with the full Shaw.
See how the first six characters are the same.
This commit here is this one.
And here's the second commit.
And here it is over here.
So nothing has changed in the repo.
The --oneline flag just alters the way the information is displayed.
It's a pretty helpful command,
if you want to quickly review a repository's commits.