Congratulations on
completing the lesson.
You learned about the history of A/B
testing beyond the use in technology,
and when A/B testing is and
is not useful.
We then introduced the business example
we'll be using throughout the course and
used a simple scenario to set
up an A/B test end to end.
In this proposed experiment,
you learned how to state and
evaluate a testable hypothesis.
This involves choosing a metric for
evaluating the change and
establishing what change in that metric
would be practically significant.
We discussed the difference
between practical and
statistical significance and how to
compute a binomial conflict interval.
You put all of that together to be
able to compute the statistical
power of an experiment and understand
the tradeoffs between power and size.
Finally, you apply those
concepts to analyzing the results
of an experiment and understanding
what you can and cannot conclude.
In the next lesson,
we'll go over what you need to keep
in mind to protect participants
in your experiments.
See you then.