Hello and welcome to this course on GitHub
and how to collaborate on a version control project.
Let's chat briefly about collaboration and why it's so important.
I mean, it's got to be important if we're creating an entire course on it.
Well, collaboration is incredibly beneficial because most of
the time you won't be working by yourself as a lone developer on a project.
You'll be working with a team,
maybe with people you don't even know,
or maybe you're contributing to an open-source project.
So being able to work collaboratively is a vital skill to have,
but it's especially important when you're working on a coding project.
One of the key aspects of collaboration is being able to communicate
clearly what you're doing and being able to work with others,
like the project's maintainers,
to see how you can contribute.
This communication can be kind of tricky when working remotely and asynchronously.
After going through this course,
you'll be able to work with others on a version control project,
use GitHub and its features to plan changes and implement those changes,
contribute to an existing repository,
and then how to add features to a project while it's in active development.
And if you're taking this course,
then I'm expecting you to already have
a pretty solid experience with version control and specifically with Git.
I've got a list of skills that I expect you to be comfortable with below this video.
Now if you're new to Git and version control in general, don't worry.
I've created a course called "Version Control with
Git" that will bring you up to speed on everything you need to know.
A link to that course is below.
So, the first thing we need to look at before we get into GitHub, collaboration,
or anything else is understanding what a remote repository is and how to work with one.
So, let's check that out now.