Can you summarize what we've
learned about variability?
>> So what we've learned so
far is that different metrics
have different variability.
And in fact, the variability may be so
high for a metric,
that's actually not practical to use
in volume in your, your experiment,
even if the metric makes a lot
of business or product sense.
Now, what we've also learned is
that to really be able to compute
the variability, we need to understand
the distribution of the underlying data.
And we looked at both analytical
techniques as well as
empirical techniques for
computing that variability.
Now, hopefully what you've
learned overall is that
computing the variability of
a metric is actually really tricky.
And so you want to be taking a lot of
care, and you want to be ensuring that
not just any random engineer or
product manager is going through and
computing the variability,
especially of complicated metrics