This is the lesson where we finally learn how to make commits of our very own.
Are you excited? Because I am.
We've laid the groundwork of learning the git init command to create a new repository,
the git clone command to copy an existing repository,
the git log command to review existing commits,
and the all important git status command to see the status of the repository.
As a side note, remember to have a download sheet with all the terms handy
during this lesson since we'll be using almost every term on that sheet.
So we have these as the foundation we'll
build on top of them in this lesson with git add,
git commit, and git diff.
With git add, you'll add files from the working directory to the staging index.
With git commit, you'll take files from the staging index and save
them in the repository which is what actually makes a commit.
The git diff command is really cool and will seem pretty
familiar actually since you've already seen its output before.
git diff displays the difference between two versions of a file.
Its output is exactly like the output of
the git log dash p command we used in the previous lesson.
So we've got a couple of new commands and one that's going to be very familiar.
Now before we can use the commit or diff commands we have to
learn how to use git add. So let's get cracking.