Carey, first let's suppose you
have a single evaluation metric,
what do you do then?
>> Well, the goal is to make
a business decision about whether your
experiment has favorably
impacted your metrics.
Analytically, that means you
want to decide if you've observed
a statistically significant
result of your experiment.
Now, typically we also want
to estimate the magnitude and
the direction of the change.
Then once you have all that information
you can make a decision about whether
you want to recommend that your business
actually launch this experiment.
>> Let's talk about the first piece.
How do you decide if the change
was statistically significant?
>> Well we're really just putting
together all the pieces we've talked
about earlier.
In Lesson 3,
we talked about characterizing the
metric, understanding how it behaves.
And in Lesson 4, we used that
information about variability
to estimate how long we needed
to run the experiment for and
size our experiment appropriately.
Now we're going to use the results
of both of those steps
to try to estimate the variability we
need to analyze the A B experiment as we
talked about at way back at
the beginning of the course.
>> And what if our results are not
statistically significant?
What do you do then?
>> Well that's a good time to take
a much longer look at your results,
especially if you were expecting
a really noticeable difference.
So for example, you might want to break
it down into different platforms,
different days of the week.
This can not only help you find bugs in
your experiment setup, but it might give
you a new hypothesis about how people
are reacting to the experiment.
Now, if this is your first go around,
you may also want to try cross checking
your results with other methods.
For example,
you could use the non parametric sign
tests that we talked about earlier.
To compare the results to what you got
from your parametric hypothesis test.
>> Sounds good.
Now let's go over some examples