We defined the estimated difference
as the experimental probability
minus the control probability.
And that comes to 0.0289.
The margin of error is equal to
the pulled standard error times 1.96,
which is our Z score for
our confidence level of 95%.
And that comes to 0.0087.
The lower bound of the confidence
interval will be d hat minus m,
which comes to 0.0202.
And the upper bound will d hat plus m,
which comes to 0.0376.
So what can we conclude
from these results?
Well, we can conclude it is highly
probable that click-through probability
changed by at least 2%.
Remember that we want to look for both
statistical and practical significance,
and here we have both.
Because 2% was our practical
significance level, and we
can be confident that we have at least
that big of a change at the 95% level.
Based on this, I would definitely
launch the new version.