To calculate the confidence interval,
first I'll
estimate the probability of a success,
which will be the point estimate.
That will be 300 divided by 2000,
which comes to 0.15.
So, 0.15 will be at the center
of the confidence interval.
Next, I'll calculate
the margin of error.
To do that, I'll need the z-score,
and it turns out that the value
is between 2.57 and 2.58.
You could really use either and it
wouldn't matter much, but I'll use 2.58.
And then that will need to be
multiplied by the standard error,
which is the square root of p hat,
times 1 minus p hat over N.
And that comes out to about 0.021.
Now, to get the upper bound, we add the
margin of error to the point estimate,
which gives 0.171, and to get the lower
bound we subtract, which gives 0.129.