Now that you know how to calculate
the number of page views you'll need for
an experiment,
I want you to consider the following
possible changes to your experiment.
And decide whether each will increase or
decrease the number of
page views you need.
First, suppose
the click-through-probability in your
control group had been higher but
still less than 50%.
Would you need more page views or
fewer to get the same sensitivity?
Second, suppose you decided to increase
your practical significance level,
which we've been calling dmin.
That is, you would no longer care about
a 2% change but you would, for example,
want to see a 3% change in
order to launch the experiment.
Third, suppose we decided to
increase your confidence level
which is also called 1 minus alpha.
For example,
maybe instead of 95% confidence,
you would choose a 99% confidence level.
Finally, suppose you wanted
to get a higher sensitivity
which is also called 1 minus beta at
the practical significance boundary.
For each case, mark whether you
think you would need to increase or
decrease the number of page views
to keep everything else the same.
I encourage you to think about what
you would expect to happen, then
try changing the numbers in the online
calculator to see what actually happens.
If you can't figure out why
a change has the effect it does,
watch the solution video for
an explanation.