Which of the following experiments might
require additional ethical review?
Specifically consider the data
that would need to be collected in
each experiment.
For the first experiment,
Audacity currently asks users if
they would like to receive a monthly
newsletter as soon as they finish
the first lesson of a course.
They want to test instead asking
users about the newsletter
as soon as they start the course.
The diversion is based on user ID.
The second experiment is similar, but
now Audacity wants to test moving the
newsletter prompt to as soon as a user
views details about
any particular course.
Since this may happen before
a user has created an account,
the diversion is based on
cookie rather than user ID.
And users who do not have an account yet
are asked for their email address,
if they wish to receive the newsletter.
In the third experiment,
Audacity changes some of the information
on a course overview page, and
measures the click through
probability on the enroll button.
Again, since users can view the course
overview page without having an account,
Audacity uses cookie based diversion.
In each case, check the box if
you think the experiment would
require additional ethical review.