Are we ready to move on to variability?
>> Not quite.
First, we have to actually decide how
we're going to compute the comparison.
What we have is, we have a value for
your experiment,
and you have a value for your control.
But, we have to actually decide, how
are you going to compute the comparison
between the experiment and the control?
>> Couldn't you take the difference
like we did in lesson 1?
>> The simplest way is just
to take the difference.
And, if you're just getting started with
experiments, or you're building up your
knowledge of a whole bunch of different
metrics, that's probably the way to go.
>> True.
But if you're running lots of
experiments, you may want to consider
computing the relative change,
as opposed to the absolute change.
In other words, the percent change.
Now, the main advantage of computing the
percent change is that you only have to
choose one practical significance
boundary, to get stability over time.
Now, the main situations that I really
see this being applicable are basically
with regards to seasonality, and
as your system is changing over time.
So, lets say you have a shopping site,
right?
And in June, most people are on
vacation, they're not shopping a lot.
So, you have fewer users, you probably
have a lower click-through rate.
Whereas, in December,
you've got loads of users, and
a much higher click-through rate.
You, if you have the same practical
significance boundary, and
across the same times, you can
basically have the same comparison.
Now, the other situation is that
if you're actually running lots of
experiments, and your system is
actually changing over time,
your metrics are probably
changing over time as well.
Again, if you're using
the relative difference,
you can stick with one
practical significance boundary
as opposed to having to change
it as your system changes.
>> Right.
The main disadvantage is really
variability.
Ratios, such as relative difference,
are not always as well behaved
as absolute differences.
So, if you're just
starting out with this, or
if you have some metrics you
don't understand that well, it's
often good to start with the absolute
difference, and then work your way up.