In the next several videos, we'll be
going over the statistics behind whether
to be surprised by 150 clicks.
If you're already familiar with
the binomial distribution,
confidence intervals, and
hypothesis testing, then you can follow
the link in the instructor's
notes to skip past this section.
So, Carrie, how do you know whether
to be surprised by 150 clicks?
In other words, how do you know how
variable your estimate is likely to be?
>> Well, there are certain distributions
that commonly arise in statistics that
can help give you some
good guidelines for
how variable your data is likely to be.
If you haven't worked with this before,
something like the bell curve that comes
up in grades is a good example
of the normal distribution and
we'll talk about that in a minute.
But for our data here,
we're going to be using a slightly
different distribution than binomial,
because instead of having continuous
data, we have successes and failures.
Now, for the binomial, we're in good
shape for this example because we can
call a click a success and
a no click visit to the page a failure.
It doesn't really matter though.
You could also use this distribution
if your data were red and blue, or
any two exclusive outcomes.
What matters is, we have exactly two
possible outcomes, click and no click,
and that our metric we're going to
compute with this is a probability.