Let's say this repository exists with
three commits and the master branches pointing at the last commit that was made.
Now, one thing to note: the orientation of these commits doesn't really matter here.
Typically I've been showing them as going horizontally,
but I had to switch them to a vertical so that I could
display all of the necessary information.
Now, this repository isn't ours.
It's some other developer's.
So we decide to fork it.
Remember that when you fork a repository,
you create an identical copy.
So these two repositories will have
the exact same commits and their branches will be pointing at the same commits.
Now to create a poll request we need some new commits in our fork.
So we clone our fork down to our local machine.
Let's create a bug fix branch and make a few commits to clean things up.
Now let's push the bug fix branch back to our fork to
get these new commits up on our remote repository.
We've done all the prep work now needed for
a pull request by pushing changes to our fork,
and now is when we'd actually create a pull request.
We'll look at how to do this on GitHub in just a second.
If the pull request is accepted by the original repository's maintainer,
the commits will be added to their repository.
A merge commit will be created combining our new commits with
their existing commits and
their master branch will move to point to this new merged commit.