Okay, let's take just a second to orient ourselves to the page.
I'm here on my personal GitHub account
and we're looking at the my-travel-plans repository.
Now this is the remote repository.
This is the my-travel-plans repo,
but up on GitHub so it's the remote one.
And this remote repository has three commits.
So we need to manually create some commits using the GitHub interface.
So we can create a new file with this create new file button.
That will take us to this page where we can name the file and then set up
some of the configurations and then here we can add our content.
So we could say this would be like app.js and I like
four spaces and then we can add some content here.
But we're not going to do this right now.
We're actually going to edit an existing file.
So let's go into the css folder and edit the app.css file.
Now, here we need to click on this kind of tucked away pencil icon to edit the file.
Now, here's our file,
and let's just scroll down and I want to get to the place where I want to edit.
Now when we hover over the destination,
let's change the heading so it rotates back to a normal position.
Now we want this rotation to happen smoothly so let's add a transition.
Now that we've added these changes we can actually scroll back to the top,
click on preview changes and then see the changes that we're about to commit.
These changes look great to me,
so let's scroll down and actually make this commit.
I think add animation to destination headings is a good commit message.
So, that works for me and I'll just commit these changes.
So we have this commit that we just made right now.
Let's go back and check out the main page.
Notice that we now have four commits when we previously had three,
and that the css folder there has been a change 11 seconds ago.
If we go inside that folder we'll see that app.css was changed 29 seconds ago.