Suppose your company is considering
collecting or storing the following data
either to use in an A/B test or
for some other purpose.
In which cases would the data
be considered sensitive?
In other words,
people would be at risk if the data
were exposed to non-trusted individuals.
First, suppose you are considering
analyzing existing census data.
Containing race, age and gender
distributions broken down by zip code.
Is this census data sensitive?
Next suppose you're interested in how
many users visit some specific websites.
So you use a source like comScore or
HitWise to gather a count of the number
of users visiting those sites each day.
ComScore and Hitwise are products
providing this kind of online analytics.
Or what if you have a mobile app
that helps diabetics track their
glucose levels, and
you want to store each glucose level and
the time it was entered?
You don't store the person's
name with the data, but
you want to know which data points
came from the same person, so
you do store an anonymous
ID with each entry.
Next, suppose you have an online game
and you store things like each time
a user gains an achievement, kills
an enemy, or advances to the next level.
Again, you associate this
information with an anonymous ID.
Or suppose you have an online
shopping company, like Amazon, and
you store the number of purchases made
on your site and the total money spent,
broken down by zip code.
Finally, suppose again you have
an online shopping company and
you want to store your users' credit
card information to save it for
their next visit.
In each case, check the box if
you think the data is sensitive.