We've got here the three sections of our repository: the working directory,
the staging index, and the repository up at the top.
Let's say our repo currently has these commits in it,
with master currently pointing at the most recent commit.
We have HEAD pointing at master,
and our files are in the working directory.
Let's shift things around a second.
These are the three places content from a reset commit will go: the working directory,
the staging index, and the trash,
meaning it'll be erased.
Running git reset HEAD's parent will move HEAD and master to the previous commit.
But what happens to the commit with the number three?
The changes that were made could be moved to the working directory or the staging index,
or they could just be thrown out.
It all depends on the flag that's used with the reset command.
Let's move this commit back.
If we run git reset without any flags,
then the changes that were made in the commit with
SHA-3 are applied to the files in the working directory.
This is because --mixed is the default.
So running get reset without a flag is the same as running it with --mixed.
So if we stage the files and commit again,
we'll get the same commit content.
We'll get a different commit SHA just because
the time stamp of the commit will be different from the original one,
but the commit content will be exactly the same.
Using the --soft flag will move
the changes that were made in the commit with SHA-3 to the staging index.
It's the same changes and now they're even staged for you.
All you have to do is run git commit to get the commit back.
Again, since the time stamp is different,
the new commit SHA will be different.
The last is the --hard flag.
This one will throw out all of the changes that were made in the commit with SHA-3.