So let's say we go to measure
the click-through probability of
the start now button.
And we see that 1,000 unique users
visit the Audacity homepage.
And 100 of those visitors clicked
the start now button at least once.
From this data, the best estimate
of the click-through probability
would be 100 divided by 1000, or 10%.
But, how sure would you
be about this estimate?
In other words,
suppose you repeated the measurement.
You had a different 1,000
users visit the site and
again you recorded how many of
them clicked the start now button.
Which results would surprise you?
Would you be surprised if
you got 100 clicks again?
101?
110?
150?
How about 900?
Check all the answers
that would surprise you.
We'll talk later about how
to quantify this, but for
right now just check the ones that you
subjectively would be surprised by.