In the previous lesson we looked at working with remote repositories.
Now we'll use those skills in this lesson to copy
another developer's repository and to start working on it.
The skills we'll be covering in this lesson are,
being able to fork a repository,
reviewing the changes that have been made on a project by other developers,
knowing what changes to make now that you have access to the repository.
One of the tools we'll be using a lot and this lesson is GIT log.
I expect you to already know the basics of GIT log and we'll be delving
a lot more into its capabilities to narrow down the information in the repository.
Sounds good? Let's check out what this whole forking thing is all about.