Our recent online example is from
Facebook and some Cornell researchers,
who studied how emotions can
be spread on social media.
Specifically, one set of randomly
selected participants saw a newsfeed
with slightly fewer negative posts and
another set saw a newsfeed with
slightly fewer positive posts.
A week later, the researchers measured
whether the posts from the participants
were more negative or positive.
For the Facebook experiment, the risk to
the participants is substantially lower
than either of the other experiments,
and there is no discussion
about the potential benefits that
might result from such a study.
Now, these are three examples of
problematic, or potentially problematic,
experiments.
Clearly, these are the exceptions to
the rule, rather than the common case.
But it is because of these
problematic experiments that IRBs, or
institutional review boards, came to be.
IRBs review possible experiments and
ensure that participants
are adequately protected.
That said, most IRBs are tied to
academic institutions and it's still
a grey area about whether Internet
studies should be reviewed by an IRB.
However, online say you should
still make protecting participants
a primary concern.
The four main principles
to consider are, one, risk.
What risk is the participant
being exposed to?
Two, benefit.
What benefits might be
the outcome of the study?
Three, choice.
What other choices do participants have?
And finally, four, privacy.
What expectation of privacy and
confidentiality do participants have?
We'll discuss each of these next.