In the first case,
the unit of analysis is a pageview.
This doesn't match the unit
of diversion, which usually
means the analytical estimate will
be an underestimate of the variance.
So, I wouldn't expect the analytic and
empirical variance to match.
In the second case,
the unit of analysis is a cookie.
Or really a daily slice
of the cookie's activity,
since I said that this metric
was being computed daily.
There isn't really a denominator to this
metric, but since the number of cookies
is what's being computed,
the cookie is the unit of analysis.
The unit of analysis is larger
than the unit of diversion
in the sense that one cookie could
generate multiple pageviews.
This is a problem, given that the unit
of diversion is a pageview, because it
means the same cookie could have events
in both the experiment group, and
the control group.
That means this metric is actually not
well defined for this experiment design.
In general,
you need your unit of diversion to be at
least as big as your unit of analysis.
In this case, cookie would work
as the unit of diversion, and
user-id would work, since one user-id
can correspond to multiple cookies.
But usually not vice versa.
But, event level diversion
is too fine grained here.
In the third case,
the unit of analysis is a user-id,
which matches the unit of diversion.
You'll never get analytic and
empirical estimates that agree exactly,
but they'll probably be
a lot closer in this case.