We have our original repository,
our fork of the original,
and then the clone of our fork.
Let's say that we forked the original repository to fix up a few mistakes.
So we have the bugfix branch that we've worked on locally and then pushed to our fork.
But while we've been working on these changes,
the original project's maintainers have
added some commits of their own to their repository.
So now, our fork and
the local repository's master branches are out of sync with the original repository.
To get these new changes in our local machine,
we need to fetch them from the original repository.
Now remember that we have a link to our remote repository because when we cloned it,
Git created a connection for us automatically and
gave this connection a short name of origin.
We can manually set up a connection to the original or source remote repository, though.
Typically, we'd name the short name upstream.
Let's add the short names origin and upstream so we can easily refer to them.
Now that we have this new upstream connection to the original remote repository,
let's display the remote branches that exist in our local repository.
Now if we fetch the commits from the upstream repository,
we'll end up with these two commits and an upstream/master branch.
These colors might be a bit misleading so let's
show how each branch relates to each remote.
Let's set local to red,
fork to yellow, and original to blue.
Both the bugfix branch and the master branch are in our local repository.
We've also pushed them to our fork.
Git knows where our remote branches are,
so the origin/bugfix and origin/master branches display in our local repository.
The original repository has just its master branch.
Because we've retrieved the upstream changes,
upstream/master displays in our local repository.
So let's go back to our original color scheme that's based on the branches.
Now if we're on our master branch and merge in the upstream/master branch,
our master branch will perform a fast-forward merge to point to
commit c. Then if we wanted to merge in the bugfix branch,
that would create a new merge commit and move master to point to it.