Okay, so we've designed and
sized the experiment.
Now, let's assume that we've run it and
analyzed the results of the experiment.
Suppose the control group had
10,072 total page views, and
the experimental group had 9,886.
These numbers aren't exactly the same
because of how people were randomly
assigned to groups.
In the control group 974 of those users
clicked the Start Now button, and
in the experimental group, 1242 did.
So, it certainly looks like more people
clicked in the experimental group, but
was this due to random variation?
To answer that, we'll need to
calculate the confidence interval for
the difference.
I'll start by calculating
the pooled probability,
that is the total number
of clicks in both groups,
divided by the total number of users,
and that comes to about 0.111.
Next, I'll calculate the pool to
standard error using the formula you
saw before, and
this comes to about 0.00445.
Now, go ahead and
finish the calculation,
by calculating the estimated difference,
or d hat, and the margin of error, or m.
Write your answers in these
boxes to four decimal places.
Then, put the upper and lower bounds of
the confidence interval in these boxes,
also to four decimal places.
Finally, would you launch the new
version of the Start Now button based on
these results?
Select yes or no.
Don't forget to consider whether
the change is greater than the practical
significance level of 2%, and
use the 95% confidence level.