Sensitivity can be a bit
tricky to calculate, so
people have a few different techniques
they might use to determine how many
page views they'll need.
First, some programming languages
have built-in libraries that can
calculate this.
You might also be able to find a table
where you can look up the answer, or
you might be able to use
an online calculator.
For the audacity experiment,
we'd like you to use the online
calculator linked in
the instructors notes.
Now on this calculator,
there are a few different pieces of
information you'll have to enter.
The baseline conversion rate in our
case means the estimated click through
probability before making the change,
and the minimum detectable effect is
what we've been calling
the practical significance level.
You'll also need to specify whether
your practical significance
total is an absolute or
a relative change.
We've been using an absolute change,
so make sure you check this option.
We'll talk more about
the difference in Lesson three.
Finally, you'll need to enter
1 minus beta and alpha.
Note that this calculator refers to
1 minus beta as statistical power,
rather than sensitivity.
Write the number of page views we'll
need in each group of the experiment
in this box.
Recall that before making the change,
we collected 1000 unique page views,
of which 100 resulted in a click,
We decided on a practical
significance level of 2%, or 0.02,
which I am calling d min, because it's
the minimum difference we care about.
And you should use alpha equals 0.05,
and
beta equals 0.2,
which is fairly standard.