I'm on a course collaboration travel plans
repository that I forked from Lam's project here.
Now, I want to make some changes on my local machine,
so I need to clone that down.
So, let's get the cloneable url.
And now, we can switch over to the terminal and clone this project.
So, I'm going to run git clone and
paste in the url to this repository to clone this down to my machine.
Now, the CD into the project.
And now, I'm going to switch over to my code editor to make some changes.
Before we switch to the code editor,
let's switch to a new branch so that all of our changes will be added to that branch,
instead of the master branch.
So, I've switched to a new branch called 'include-richards-destinations'.
I want mom to come with me to my destinations,
so I'm going to add those here to her project.
I'm going to add these as three different commits because we're going to
be using those three separate commits later in the course.
So let's scroll down here and I'm going to add Florida to this list.
And now to add the styling for Florida over here.
So, I have these two sets of changes, let's commit them.
Before committing, I always like to run
a quick git diff to make sure I'm adding everything.
So, let's run git diff.
I've got the Florida css changes and
then the Florida html changes. Everything looks good.
So, let's add these files and then commit them.
Now, let's have the destination to Paris.
Copy the html over here and edit the I.D.
to Paris and edit the actual heading to Paris,
then I'll copy the styling and update this to Paris and change the background color.
Save this file and save this file and then,
back to the terminal to make another commit.
Let's check the diff for this Paris change.
So, we have the css file.
We have these changes, the html file,
we have these. Looks great.
So, I'll add these changes and then, I'll commit this.
And finally, let's add the destination to Scotland.
So, copy the html one more time,
changes to Scotland, change the heading to Scotland.
Now, change the css over here,
change this to Scotland and then changing the background color.
Now, let's save the css file and save the html file,
and back to the terminal one last time. Let's run get diff.
We've got the css change and the html change.
Awesome. So, I'll add these files and then I'll commit them.
Let's take a quick look at the git log.
We can see that our new
'include-richards-destinations' branch is up here while the master branch is down here,
but especially the remote origin master branch is right here on this commit.
So, both of these are on this commit while our new branch is up here.
So, we just need to push this branch up to
our remote repository to get these commits on the remote.
So, let's push to the origin remote this branch.
I'll enter in my username and then my password.
That created this new branch up on the remote repository.
Let's check that out.
I'm on my remote repository on the master branch.
Now, I need to switch over to the other branch that I just pushed,
so that we can see those changes.
Now, I can look at the index file and then,
here are the changes that I've added- the destinations that I've added.
Now, if I check out Lam's project
her remote repository and scroll down in the index file,
we'll see that those changes are not added there.
So, when I pushed,
my changes only went to my project, not to hers.