We're looking at the log of commits that have been made in this repository.
This is one commit, here is another.
Look at all of the information that the log is displaying.
It's showing the commits Shaw,
the person who made the commit,
the date the commit was made,
and the message for the commit.
This is just a short description of what changes were made in this commit.
Now these are just the first three or so commits that can fit on the screen.
There are plenty more.
How do I know that? The colon here
means that there are more lines of output to be displayed.
If you're familiar with the command line,
GIT uses the less program as its pager.
If you're not familiar with less or pagers that's no problem.
A pager is used to page through content.
This is just the command line e-way of scrolling.
Press either the J key or the down arrow to scroll down one line at a time.
To scroll up press the K key or the up arrow.
You'll know you've reached the very last commit when the colon changes to the word end.
To get out of the pager just press the Q key.