Now consider invariant metrics for
another experiment.
This time, Audacity changes the location
of the sign in button to see if they can
get users to sign in sooner.
The sign in button currently appears
on the course list page, and if a user
who isn't signed in tries to enroll in
a course, they are prompted to sign in.
But in the experiment group, the sign
in button is added to every page,
including the home page.
The unit of diversion is a cookie,
since Audacity wants
a consistent experience across
the sign-in sign-out boundary.
Again, which metrics would
make good invariants?
Number of events, click through rate or
CTR on the start now button,
the probability of a user
enrolls in a course.
The sign in rate, that is,
the rate at which users who are not
signed in, complete the sign in process.
Or finally,
the average load time of the video.
Again, check each metric that would be
a good invariant for this experiment.