I have a confession to make.
When I first learned about the oneline flag for git log,
I was really excited about it.
Now I didn't have to scroll and scroll and scroll to read all of the comment messages.
It worked for a couple of times until one time I got this.
Why isn't it working now?
I tried restarting the terminal.
That didn't do anything. I restarted my computer and that didn't help.
Finally, I actually read Git's helpful error message carefully.
I had typed out "online" instead of oneline.
It says, "fatal: unrecognized argument: --online."
Online is unrecognized, which means Git doesn't know about it.
This error message, or something similar,
is common to run into while programming.
So, keep an eye out for it.
Unfound or unrecognized arguments often mean a simple spelling mistake.
So, the moral of the story, spelling is important.
Make sure you actually spell things correctly.
Also, Git will try and provide helpful feedback.
Make sure you read it carefully.