Lessons three, four and
five will dive into the technical
details of how to run A/B tests online.
Before we do that, though,
we wanted to talk about how to consider
the ethics of your AB test and
how to protect your users.
>> This lesson gives a high level
overview of the questions and
principles that you should think
about while designing, running, and
analyzing your experiment.
We'll start with some case studies
to motivate the importance of
thinking through the ethics.
And then go through the four
major principles to consider,
before summarizing the main principles
that you should be answering for
your proposed AB test.
>> Many people and
companies don't necessarily give
much thought to these issues.
After all if your a streaming
video service, a review site, or
your selling handmade goods or meals,
is the service your providing really
affecting people to the degree where
you need to think about ethics?
>> Realistically in most
cases that's probably right.
>> But, you know, you can get to
a gray line pretty quickly if you
think about how integrated these
services are in people's lives.
Even for streaming video,
what if those videos are used
to teach the Heimlich Maneuver?
>> Our goal in this lesson is to
highlight the types of issues that
you should keep in mind as you
design and run experiments.
Because those issues may
affect little decisions,
from what type of user identification
you use to divert someone into
the experiment, to what data you capture
or whether you run the A/B test at all.
>> That said, this will only
be a high level introduction.
Many of these issues are highly nuanced.
And our goal is to give
you an idea of the basics.
If you're really running into
potential tests that are questionable,
which hopefully these principles
will help you determine,
then you should be seeking
expert advice and counsel.