In this lesson, we first learned about
what the different possible choices for
a unit of diversion is and
why we might have a preference.
We also discussed how
to choose a population.
We then walked through the irrative
process of sizing your experiment, and
how to choose how long your
experiment will run for.
When you put these decisions together
with what we discussed in lesson one
about statistical power and
practical significance,
you have gone through all the decisions
necessary to design your experiment.
In the next lesson, we'll be finishing
up our course by going through how to
evaluate the results from our AB test.