This is a fork.
This is the noun form of the word.
When we talk about forks in version control,
we're not talking about this.
We're talking about the verb or action version of the word.
Let's say you're out hiking on a trail and all of a sudden,
it splits into two paths.
We'd say that the road forked into two different paths.
So, that's the verb form of the word.
In the version control world,
forking is a split,
but it's an identical split.
To fork a repository means to split it into an identical copy.
Now, forking is not a Git thing,
you can't run git fork on the command line.
There's no fork subcommand.
It's something provided by the hosting environment.
GitHub is our hosting environment,
so GitHub has a fork button that lets you fork a repository.
If you're on a repository's page on GitHub and click the fork button,
you make a copy of that repository and bring it over to your own account.
So this is what it means to fork something: make
an identical copy and become the owner of that copy.