For the next few videos, we're going
to go over some more examples of when
you can and can't use A/B tests.
As well as some other techniques you
can use instead of A/B testing, and
a brief history of A/B testing.
After that, I'll introduce the example
A/B test that we'll be using for
the rest of this lesson.
So if you'd rather skip to this point,
you can do so
by following the link in
the Instructor's Notes.
Right now, I'm going to go over a list
of possible changes you might consider
using A/B testing for, and
ask you to decide when A/B
testing would be appropriate.
First, suppose an online
shopping company,
like Amazon, wants to know whether
their site is complete, or
whether there are products users
want to buy, that they don't have.
Check this box if you think they could
answer this question using an A/B test.
Second, suppose the company
already has a free service.
Maybe they have a to-do list app and
they want to provide a premium service
that offers additional functionality.
To access the premium service,
users would need to upgrade,
create a log in, and
explore the new functionality.
Check this box if you think the company
should test out this change,
using A/B testing.
Third, consider a site that provides
a list of Movie recommendations for
users, such as Netflix.
They create a new algorithm to
rank the possible recommendations.
Could this be tested using AB testing?
Finally, suppose you wanted to change
your backend infrastructure, which could
impact how quickly the page loads, what
results users see, and other things.
Would an A/B test be appropriate
to test this change?