Which of the following
experiments are risky enough that
Audacity might want to limit
the number of users who are exposed?
That is, for which experiments do
you think it would make sense to
run the experiment for longer, but
expose fewer total users to the change?
First, suppose Audacity changes
the database they're using in their
back end.
Second, consider the experiment
from lesson one,
where Audacity changed the color
of the start now button.
How risky was this experiment?
Next, suppose Audacity tests
changing the account creation.
Before, each user had to create
an account with a new password, but
now Audacity tests
allowing Facebook login.
Finally, what if Audacity
tests changing the order of
the courses on the course list page?
For each change, check the box if you
think this is a high enough risk change
to limit the number of
users who are exposed.