You said consistency was the first
of three main considerations.
What's the second?
>> The second is ethical considerations.
Do you remember back in lesson two,
when we went through the principles and
questions that you should keep
in mind as you're designing,
running and analyzing your experiment?
Well, one of those principles and
questions was regarding what data you're
collecting, and
whether the data is identified or not.
If you are using a User ID then by
definition the data is identified.
And so you have all of those security
and confidentiality questions that you
have to really answer if you're
going to gather data by User ID.
Now if your internal processes
are really good you are going to be good
tackling that challenge.
But if not you are,
you want to think through whether you
want to go through all of that work.
Now, the other issue that comes
up with the choice of unit and
of diversion is that
of informed consent.
If you're using the User ID,
you know who the user is, and
you can plausibly get user consent.
If you're doing a vent based or
a cookie based diversion,
you don't really know who the user is.
It's not really a, necessarily,
a consistent experience.
And so user consent becomes
a little bit less of an issue.