For online A/B testing then,
the questions come down to, 1,
are users informed about
the data gathering in some form,
such as via a terms and
services, or a privacy policy?
2, what user identifiers are tied
to the data being gathered?
Especially if there is personally
identifiable information, such as name,
email, phone number, address,
then the data collected becomes much
more sensitive, and subject to review.
3, what type of data is being collected?
How sensitive is it?
Is there health or
financial data being collected?
4, what level of confidentiality and
security is the data subject to?
Can anyone at the company access
the data, especially if it is personally
identifiable, or is the data secured
with accesses logged and audited?
It is worth noting that these concerns
should apply to online services, period,
regardless of whether AB
testing is happening or not.
Now, one additional question
that often gets asked is,
what about informed consent?
Informed consent is a process
by which participants
are told that the risks that they may
face if they participate in the study.
What benefits might result.
What other options they have.
What data is being gathered, and
how that data is being handled.
Typically, informed consent is
a process by which participants
are given a document that
has all of that information.
And then, participants can
choose whether to participate in
the study, or not.
When IRB's are assessing a study,
they also get to decide whether
an informed consent is required, or not.
While many people may think that
informed consent is required
whenever a study is considered
human subject research.
In fact, situations where informed
consent may not be required
are when the risk is minimal, and the
data being gathered is not identified.