Often in A/B testing, you'll find that a
metric you want is difficult to measure.
This can happen because you
don't have access to the data or
because the metric would simply
take too long to collect.
In the audacity example,
the last level of the funnel
was how many students get jobs.
And both of these problems
apply to this metric.
Audacity probably doesn't know when
one of its students gets a job.
And even if it did,
getting a job can be a long process.
So, it might not be possible to use
this as a metric for most experiments.
Now I'm going to go over
some additional metrics, and
I want you to choose which ones you
think would be hard to measure.
First, suppose Audacity
wanted to measure the rate
of students returning to
take a second course.
That is, the number of users who
complete one class and then start
a second divided by the total number of
users who complete at least one class.
Would this be a difficult metric to use?
Or what if an online
shopping site like Amazon
wanted to measure the average happiness
of shoppers who complete a purchase?
And finally, suppose a search engine
like Google wanted to measure
the probability that a user finds
the information they were looking for
within their search results.
And for each metric check the box,
if you think this metric would
be difficult to measure, for
either of these two reasons.